topic_id,query,facet_id,facet_desc,question,question2_case,answer,history,distractor
32,I'm looking for information on web design and hosting.,F0780,Find sites that offer free DNS hosting.,how much data do you need stored,similar_yes_no,"I haven't decided yet, I need to find website that offers free DNS hosting first.","[{'question': 'would you like to register a domain name', 'answer': 'yes specifically for free'}]",id like to know what services are available at the ontario ca airport
160,What are the best recepies for grilling,F0245,Find instructions for grilling chicken.,are you interested in kabob recipes,repeated,I don't know.,"[{'question': 'are you interested in kabob recipes', 'answer': 'no i need to know how to grill chicken'}]",no im looking if biodegradable products exist for dog waste disposal
153,Tell me about Pocono,F0212,Find information about the Pocono Raceway in Pennsylvania.,are you interested in lodgings,similar_no_no,I am not interested in that topic,"[{'question': 'are you looking for the information about split rock restore', 'answer': 'no pocono raceway in pennsylvania'}]",no i whcih to learn more about the voyagers learning programs
12,how to hire disc jockey,F0088,What jobs are available for disc jockeys?,do you need to book a dj for an event,similar_yes_no,"Yes, as I am looking to hire a well-known and respectable DJ.","[{'question': 'would you like to read about dj employment', 'answer': 'yes'}]",yes but i would also like information about all hayrides in pennsylvania
136,Tell me about american military university.,F0146,What are the registration requirements for enrolling at American Military University?,what degree in particular would you like to know more about from the american military unviersity,repeated,just in general what are the registration requirements?,"[{'question': 'what degree in particular would you like to know more about from the american military unviersity', 'answer': 'i need to know the registration requirements'}]",no i want to know how to treat it
29,Tell me about ps 2 games?,F0733,What are the specifications of the PlayStation 2 console?,which ps 2 game genres are you interested in,similar_yes_no,Can you tell me what the specifications of the PS2 system are?,"[{'question': 'are you referring to playstation 2 games', 'answer': 'yes i am'}]",no
112,Is Kenmore heater good,F0058,"information about Kenmore gas water heaters: specifically, features, energy consumption and safety thereof",would you like to know how much a kenmore gas water heater is,repeated,No more like the safety and features of them.,"[{'question': 'would you like to know how much a kenmore gas water heater is', 'answer': 'no i need information on them'}]",no i want to find thepowerwasheradvisorcom website
65,Tell me about Korean language.,F0926,Find a Korean/English bilingual dictionary.,are you interested in the history of the korean language,similar_yes_no,Nope just a dictionary that is both in Korean and English.,"[{'question': 'are you looking for a dictionary', 'answer': 'yes i want to find a koreanenglish bilingual dictionary'}]",no i want you to navigate to wwwthepowerwasheradvisorcom
241,How to use wiki?,F0559,Find information about what a wiki is.,is a rich text editor something you are familiar with,similar_no_no,"I'm not sure, I am interested in learning about wikis.","[{'question': 'what would you like to know about ward cunningham inventor of th wiki', 'answer': 'no id like to know what a wiki is'}]",no i would like to know how that quote has been interpereted over time
137,tell me about rock and gem shows,F0150,rock and gem shows that offer lapidary classes,would you like directions to local rock and gem shows,similar_yes_no,"no, i want to know which ones have lapidary classes","[{'question': 'are you looking for information about upcoming rock and gem shows', 'answer': 'yes ones that have lapidary classes'}]",yes
115,Tell me about the pacific northwest laboratory.,F0066,"career opportunities at PNL: what openings are currently available, what educational background is required, what prior experience is needed",are you looking for research papers,repeated,No I want to know what career opportunities are available at PNL.,"[{'question': 'are you looking for research papers', 'answer': 'no'}]",no i am looking for general information about computer memory
75,Find information about tornadoes,F0966,Find information about forecasting tornadoes.,are you interested in tornado safety,similar_no_no,Maybe.  I want to know about forecasting tornadoes though.,"[{'question': 'would you like historic information', 'answer': 'no i want to know about how tornadoes are forecast'}]",no im looking for tutorials
34,Tell me about cell phones.,F0787,What free phones are available from different vendors?,are you looking for a new phone with a specific carrier,repeated,I am looking for a free phone from any carrier,"[{'question': 'are you looking for a new phone with a specific carrier', 'answer': 'no any carrier will do but the phone has to be free'}]",no i am looking for thing to do in cass county mo
39,Give me information about Disneyland hotel.,F0806,What hotels are near Disneyland?,are you looking for directions to a disneyland hotel,similar_yes_no,"Yes, that's exactly what I'm looking for.","[{'question': 'do you want to know how much it costs to stay here', 'answer': 'yes and the name and locations of hotels'}]",i dont know
199,Tell me about fybromyalgia,F0405,What are the primary symptoms or signs of fybromyalgia?,are you looking for a diet to help manage fibromyalgia,repeated,"no, i want to know characteristics of fybromyalgia.","[{'question': 'are you looking for a diet to help manage fibromyalgia', 'answer': 'no i am intereested in the symptoms of fybromyalgia'}]",yes but i also need more general onformation about solar panels too
67,I'm looking for information on VLDL levels,F0933,"What is the difference between LDL, HDL, and VLDL?",would you like a recommendation on nearby doctors who check cholesteral levels,similar_no_no,"No, I need to know the difference between LDL, HDL AND VLDL.","[{'question': 'are you interested in ways to reduce vldl levels', 'answer': 'no i want to know the difference between ldl hdl and vldl'}]",no i am intrested in the sale of arocky mountain news
145,Tell me about vines for shade.,F0178,"ideas on using plant vines to shade an area on or around my house from the sun, like training them on an inexpensive trellis or up a wall or fence",do you want to know where to buy vines for shade,similar_yes_no,"No, I want to know ideas for using them on a trellis.","[{'question': 'do you want to know the best vines for providing shade', 'answer': 'yes i want to know which species of vines would be the best for shade'}]",no
129,Tell me information about Iowa's food stamp program,F0119,Find the homepage for Iowa's Food Assistance Program?,are you referring to a food stamp program that is current or a historical one,repeated,I mean the current food assistance program page,"[{'question': 'are you referring to a food stamp program that is current or a historical one', 'answer': 'i need the current websit of the iowa food assistance program'}]",yes and other ideas on how to celebrate the day
92,Find information about the wall,F1042,"Find information about the movie ""Pink Floyd The Wall"".",would you like to know the rules of the wall game show,similar_yes_no,"No, I want to know about the movie, Pink Floyd the Wall..","[{'question': 'are you looking for a specific movie', 'answer': 'yes am looking for the movie pink floyd the wall'}]",i need illinois state tax forms
140,Information about east ridge high school.,F0165,"information about the sports program at East Ridge High School in Clermont, Florida",are you interested in east ridge high school latest news,similar_no_no,"Specifically, I want to know about the athletic program at East Ridge High in Clermont, Florida.","[{'question': 'do you need directions to east ridge high school', 'answer': 'not related to queryquestion'}]",no i am not looking for biodegradable dog clean up i just want dog clean up bags under 15
76,Find information on raised gardens.,F0967,Find plans for building a raised garden bed.,do you need information on materials needed,repeated,I want what I previoulsy asked for.,"[{'question': 'do you need information on materials needed', 'answer': 'no i want to find plans'}]",i want to kno wthe calorie count of each item
34,Tell me about cell phones.,F0788,Find information on prepaid cell phones. What companies offer them? What kind of phones are available?,are you interested in a specific brand of cell phone,similar_yes_no,"No, only that it's prepaid.","[{'question': 'were you looking for how cell phones work', 'answer': 'yes what companies have prepaid phones and what kind are available'}]",i would like all information available on hpv atypical squamous cells and cervical cancer
115,Tell me about the pacific northwest laboratory.,F0066,"career opportunities at PNL: what openings are currently available, what educational background is required, what prior experience is needed",do you need any specific information about pnl,repeated,Yes I want to know what positions they are hiring for.,"[{'question': 'do you need any specific information about pnl', 'answer': 'yes im looking for information pertaining to careers at pnl'}]",id like to view howw the supreme court has interperated the quote throught the years
150,How can one can become highway patrol,F0197,What are the requirements to become a Tennessee Highway Patrol State Trooper?,are you interested to fill a survey for them,similar_no_no,"No, more so how to actually become a highway patrol state trooper.","[{'question': 'are you interested in how much a patrol officer makes per year', 'answer': 'no i want to know how to become one'}]",no i would like to see some detailed geographic maps
121,Tell me about the sit and reach test.,F0095,How is the sit and reach test properly done?,would you like to know where the test is used in,similar_yes_no,"No, I want to know how to properly perform the test.","[{'question': 'do you want to know how to perform this test', 'answer': 'yes i do'}]",please show me where i can download illionios state tax forms
180,Tell me about hotels in New York.,F0338,I want to book a room in a hotel that's on Times Square in New York City.,do you need direction to your new york hotel,similar_no_no,"Yes, hotels near the Times Square in New Yorks City specifically","[{'question': 'what is your price range', 'answer': 'i dont know the answer to this'}]",no just the brands
26,How can I lower my heart rate?,F0626,How can I lower my heart rate?,do you have any medical conditions,repeated,"I am not sure, can you tell me how to lower my heart rate regardless?","[{'question': 'do you have any medical conditions', 'answer': 'im not sure but can you tell me some general method anyway'}]",yes as well as what products it is levied on
75,Find information about tornadoes,F0964,Find videos and pictures of tornadoes.,would you like historic information,similar_no_no,"Not really, just some recorded media of tornadoes.","[{'question': 'are you looking for information on weather', 'answer': 'no just some pictures and videos'}]",yes i would please include states and their capitals
40,what are the popular jobs in Michigan,F0817,Find career resources and information on job seeking in Michigan.,do you need need information related to unemployed services in michigan,similar_yes_no,"No, I want to see information on jobs.","[{'question': 'can i take you to the resource page at the michworks website', 'answer': 'yes please show me the resources page'}]",no i want to get reviews of the ritz carlton lake las vegas
157,I'm looking for information on the beatles rock band,F0227,What albums did the Beatles release?,do you want a list of their songs,repeated,"No, I'd like the list of Albums they released.","[{'question': 'do you want a list of their songs', 'answer': 'no i want to know the actual album names'}]",no i am looking to achieve it in the workplace and manage it
89,Give me information on OCD.,F1025,Find information about OCD in children and how to identify it.,are you looking for documentaries of people who live with ocd,similar_no_no,"No, I want to know how to identify it in children.","[{'question': 'are you looking for treatment for ocd', 'answer': 'no im looking for general information about ocd and how to identify it in children'}]",yes what tourist attractions are in cass county mo
135,Tell me about source of the nile,F0145,map of the Nile River basin,are you interested in the origin of the nile,similar_yes_no,Yes I need to know what water source flows into the Nile by seeing a map of the Nile River Basin.,"[{'question': 'are you referring to the nile river', 'answer': 'yes the nile river and its basin'}]",yes including the nearby areas of the capitol
168,What are the causes of lipoma tumors,F0280,Which animals are known to present lipomas?,are you looking for the definition to lipoma,repeated,"no, just want to know which animals are susceptible to lipomas.","[{'question': 'are you looking for the definition to lipoma', 'answer': 'no i am looking for animals that get lipomas'}]",i want to know how the phrase all men are created equal has been interpreted by the united states supreme court through out history
198,Tell me more about indiana state fairgrounds.,F0404,Find a map for the Indiana State Fairgrounds.,do you need an event schedule for the indiana state fairgrounds,similar_no_no,I want to see a map of it instead.,"[{'question': 'would you like the history of indiana state fairgrounds', 'answer': 'no im looking for a map of the indiana state fairgrounds'}]",i dont know
172,I'm looking for information on becoming a paralegal,F0302,What ABA-approved certificate programs are there?,do you want to know the responsibilities of a paralegal,repeated,"No, find me information about ABA certificate programs","[{'question': 'do you want to know the responsibilities of a paralegal', 'answer': 'no i want information about aba approve certificate programs'}]",i need to find a hotel near ontario airport in california
140,Information about east ridge high school.,F0165,"information about the sports program at East Ridge High School in Clermont, Florida",are you looking for east ridge high school in woodbury mn,similar_yes_no,"No, the one in Clermont, FL and I need the sports program information website.","[{'question': 'are you searching for east ridge high school located in clermont fl', 'answer': 'yes'}]",yes im looking for free tutorials about setting up a diversity program
23,What is yahoo,F0530,"Find information about Yahoo!, the company.",are you referring to a crazy person,similar_no_no,Find information about Yahoo!,"[{'question': 'are you referring to the insane person across the street', 'answer': 'no i want information about yahoo'}]",yes how to install
78,I'm looking for information on dieting,F0979,Find recommendations for dieting and exercising.,do you want to learn about the history of dieting,similar_yes_no,i want to know recommendations on what i should do for a diet and exercise,"[{'question': 'are you looking for dieting that involves no medications', 'answer': 'yes and i am looking for other dieting methods'}]",no i am interested in computer memory
76,Find information on raised gardens.,F0970,Find photos of raised garden beds.,what specific supply would you like to buy for your raised garden,repeated,No I'm just looking for photos of raised garden beds.,"[{'question': 'what specific supply would you like to buy for your raised garden', 'answer': 'none'}]",i dont know
138,I'm looking for information on jax chemical company,F0152,contact information for Jax Chemical Company,do you need product information,similar_yes_no,"No, I only need contact information.","[{'question': 'do you need info on jax chemical company', 'answer': 'yes specifically for contacting them'}]",yes along with other major battles
72,Find information about the sun.,F0955,Find the homepage for the Baltimore Sun newspaper.,are you interested in the suns life cycle,similar_no_no,"no, I am looking for the website for a newspaper. It is called The Baltimore Sun","[{'question': 'are you looking for how long it takes light from the sun to get to the earth', 'answer': 'no i am trying to find the website for the newspaper baltimore sun'}]",no i am looking for thing to do in cass county mo
61,I’m looking for information on worm,F0909,Find information about the Conficker worm.,do you want to know how many different types of worms there are,repeated,"No, I'm interested in a computer worm called conflicker.","[{'question': 'do you want to know how many different types of worms there are', 'answer': 'no i want information specifically about the conflicker worm'}]",yes promo coupons
88,Where can I find information about forearm pain?,F1019,Find information about tendinitis in the forearms.,are you worried your forearm pain means you have a broken bone,similar_no_no,No I just want general info on tendinitis in the forearm.,"[{'question': 'are you looking for causes of forearm pain', 'answer': 'no i need information specifically on tendinitis'}]",im looking for dog waste bags that are biodegradable
97,I'm looking for information about South Africa,F1058,Find maps of South Africa.,are you moving to south africa,similar_yes_no,No. I just wnat to see maps.,"[{'question': 'do you want a map of south africa', 'answer': 'yes'}]",when is the kentucky derby
178,How to cook pork tenderlion,F0326,How do I grill a pork tenderloin on a gas grill?,do you need to cook a pork tenderloin,repeated,"Yes, I'd like to cook on a gas grill.","[{'question': 'do you need to cook a pork tenderloin', 'answer': 'yes on a gas grill'}]",yes i am looking for illinois state tax forms
198,Tell me more about indiana state fairgrounds.,F0402,Find driving directions to the Indiana State Fairgrounds.,do you need an event schedule for the indiana state fairgrounds,similar_yes_no,I need driving directions,"[{'question': 'do you need directions to the indiana state fairgrounds', 'answer': 'yes i would like driving directions to the indiana state fairgrounds'}]",no im not
78,I'm looking for information on dieting,F0979,Find recommendations for dieting and exercising.,are you looking for dieting tips,repeated,Yes tips and recommendations.,"[{'question': 'are you looking for dieting tips', 'answer': 'yes and exercise tips as well'}]",no id like to know more information about the fruit
172,I'm looking for information on becoming a paralegal,F0301,What training is required to become a paralegal?,are you looking for a specific web page,similar_no_no,I just want to know about requirements to be a paralegal.,"[{'question': 'do you want to know colleges in your area where you can study to be a paralegal', 'answer': 'no i am looking for training requirements'}]",no i am interested in arts and crafts
69,Find sewing instructions for me,F0942,Find materials for teaching sewing to children.,using needle and thread or a sewing machine,similar_yes_no,please fine materials for teaching a child to use a sewing machine.,"[{'question': 'would you like instructions on how to use a sewing machine', 'answer': 'yes but for teaching it to children'}]",yes the ritz carlton located in lake las vegas for directions
131,What is equal opportunity employer?,F0131,Find the homepage of the Equal Employment Opportunity Commission.,would you like to know the history of the equal opportunity employer act,similar_no_no,"no, i just need the homepage url","[{'question': 'are you looking for specific information regarding an equal opportunity employer', 'answer': 'no i want to find the homepage of the eeoc'}]",i am interested in the citys historical background
60,Tell me about Bellevue.,F0904,Find the homepage of Bellevue University.,would you like to see notable residents of bellevue washington,repeated,"no, do you have the homepage of bellevue university?","[{'question': 'would you like to see notable residents of bellevue washington', 'answer': 'no take me to the bellevue university homepage'}]",no i am trying to understand more about cultural diversity and prejudice
112,Is Kenmore heater good,F0059,retailers of and price information for Kenmore gas water heaters,are you troubleshooting or trying to repair the unit,similar_yes_no,i want to know who sells kenmore gas water heaters and how much they are.,"[{'question': 'are you iinterested in a kenmore gas water heater', 'answer': 'yes i need to know the price information for the kenmore gas water heaters'}]",no i am looking for information about degree programs
93,Information about raffles,F1043,Find the homepage of Raffles Hotel in Singapore.,are you looking for raffle tickets in your area to purchase,similar_no_no,"No, I want know know about the Raffles Hotel.","[{'question': 'are you interested in buying tickets to a raffle', 'answer': 'no i want to know about the singapore hotel called raffles'}]",no i want to know more about the kiwi bird
87,who invented music,F1013,Find information on the history of rock and roll music.,do you want information on the person who invented music,repeated,Find information on the history of rock and roll music.,"[{'question': 'do you want information on the person who invented music', 'answer': 'no i am looking for the history of rock music'}]",i dont know
149,Tell me about uplift at yellowstone national park,F0190,information on ground elevation changes and movement resulting from ongoing low-level geothermal activity at Yellowstone National Park,what makes people think the yellowstone volcano will erupt soon,similar_yes_no,Recent information on the elevation of the ground in the yellowstone national park,"[{'question': 'can i tell you about the north american plate that moves causing the eventual destruction of the volcano in yellowstone park', 'answer': 'yes please'}]",no not really
14,I'm interested in dinosaurs,F0161,"I want to find pictures of dinosaurs that I can color in, as in a coloring book.",are you interested in home decor items that are dinosaur related,repeated,"no, I want what I said before.","[{'question': 'are you interested in home decor items that are dinosaur related', 'answer': 'no i need coloring books that are dinosaur related'}]",no i want to see reviews on the pampered chefs programs products and recipes
105,Tell me about sonoma county medical services.,F0025,"What medical services are available in Sonoma County, California?",is this for an emergancy,similar_yes_no,"I am not sure, I would like the more general information.","[{'question': 'do you want information on the differenct services that are provided', 'answer': 'yes'}]",no i am looking for flight information for the airport
92,Find information about the wall,F1039,"Where can I buy Pink Floyd's album, ""The Wall""?",are you looking for a specific movie,similar_no_no,"No, I'm looking for the music album, The Wall, by Pink Floy.","[{'question': 'do you neeed dry wall products', 'answer': 'no im looking for the album the wall by pink floyd'}]",no i just need to find some information
60,Tell me about Bellevue.,F0903,"Find information about Bellevue Hospital Center in New York, NY.",are you looking for a hospital in new york ny,repeated,Yes Bellevue Hospital in Manhattan NY,"[{'question': 'are you looking for a hospital in new york ny', 'answer': 'yes information on bellevue hospital new york ny'}]",no i want to find out about careers for computer programmers
161,Tell me about furniture for small spaces.,F0251,How important is the scale of furniture in small spaces?,have you got any specific question regarding furniture size,similar_no_no,Yes I want to know if size and scale is important.,"[{'question': 'are you interesting in buying furniture', 'answer': 'no i am interested in the scale of furniture in small spaces not buying furniture'}]",no i want to know where i can purchase replacement parts for pressure washers
171,Tell me about ron howard.,F0298,Find biographical information on director Ron Howard.,do you want to know more about ron howards directing career,similar_yes_no,"I'd like some biographical information on him, actually.","[{'question': 'are you interested in ron howards life story and career highlights', 'answer': 'yes'}]",maybe i want to find reviews about it first
34,Tell me about cell phones.,F0787,What free phones are available from different vendors?,did you want to know what the most popular cell phones are,repeated,"no, which offers free phones","[{'question': 'did you want to know what the most popular cell phones are', 'answer': 'no id like to know about free phones specifically'}]",yes
93,Information about raffles,F1043,Find the homepage of Raffles Hotel in Singapore.,would you like to book a room in raffles hotel in dubai,similar_no_no,"Not yet, I just want to see the homepage of the hotel.","[{'question': 'are you looking for raffle tickets in your area to purchase', 'answer': 'no the raffles hotel'}]",i dont know
211,What is Madagascar known for?,F0467,What is Madagascar known for?,would you like to know what they are known for exporting,similar_yes_no,I just want general information of what madagascar is known for.,"[{'question': 'are you looking for tourist attractions in madagascar', 'answer': 'yes and id like to know what it is known for'}]",no i need to know the common name for angular cheilitis
42,I’m looking for the music man.,F0822,Find lyrics for songs from The Music Man.,do you want to know the cast of the music man,similar_yes_no,"Not the cast, I'm interested in knowing which songs are in The Music Man.","[{'question': 'are you looking for lyrics from the songs from the music man', 'answer': 'yes i am'}]",yes specifically what are the degree requirements for a typical cs program
4,How to change the toilet in the house,F0814,What companies manufacture bidets?,what brand is your toilet,repeated,"My toilet is not a bidet, I want to know which companies make bidets.","[{'question': 'what brand is your toilet', 'answer': 'i want to know which companies make bidets'}]",no i want a photograph
140,Information about east ridge high school.,F0164,"home page for East Ridge High School in Chattanooga, Tennessee",do you need directions to east ridge high school,similar_yes_no,"No, I want to see the homepage.","[{'question': 'are you seaching for east ridge high school community education', 'answer': 'yes i am'}]",no i am looking for poems written for the day
70,to be or not to be that is the question,F0947,Find famous quotes from Shakespeare's plays.,are you talking about a psychology course,similar_yes_no,No show me some famous quotes that come from Shakespeare's most famous plays.,"[{'question': 'do you want to know where the quote came from', 'answer': 'yes i want some background of all shakespeare quotes'}]",id like to view howw the supreme court has interperated the quote throught the years
121,Tell me about the sit and reach test.,F0093,"Find out what the ""sit and reach test"" is.",do you want to purchase a box to measure with,repeated,"no, what is the sit and reach test actually?","[{'question': 'do you want to purchase a box to measure with', 'answer': 'no'}]",yes on a pap smear test
98,Find me information on sat,F1061,Find general information about the SATs.,what would you like to schedule for saturday,similar_no_no,I am not interested in scheduling.,"[{'question': 'are you searching for your sat scores', 'answer': 'no i want general information about sat scores'}]",no i am looking for famous generals who fought in the united states civil war
228,Tell me more about Hawain volcanos,F0525,I am looking for the history of and a summary of the work performed at the Hawaiian Volcano Observatories.,do you want a list of all the volcano observatories in hawaii,similar_yes_no,"Sure, but I also want to know their history and the summary of work they perform.","[{'question': 'would you like to know the histories of the observatories', 'answer': 'yes'}]",no i am looking for poems that were written for poem in your pocket day
130,What are characteristics of Uranus,F0127,"Find information on Uranus suitable for elementary-to-middle school students, such as lesson content or interactive sites.",are you wondering what probe visited uranus,similar_yes_no,"Yes, especially how long it took to get there.","[{'question': 'do you want to know how old it is estimated to be', 'answer': 'yes and some other general information about the planet'}]",just the home page of the website
81,Tell me about Afganistan.,F0993,Find information about the war in Afghanistan.,do you want to know about the wars fought in afghanistan,repeated,"I would, yes.","[{'question': 'do you want to know about the wars fought in afghanistan', 'answer': 'yes'}]",yes
148,What is martha stewart and imclone?,F0187,opinions regarding the insider trading case brought against Martha Stewart,are you looking for a specific web site,similar_no_no,Sure if it has opinions about the Martha Stewart case.,"[{'question': 'are you looking for specific information about martha stewart and imcones age', 'answer': 'no im looking for opinions regarding martha stewarts insider trading case'}]",yes i would need very detailed information on a map of the united states
28,I'm interested in InuYasha,F0700,I'm looking for InuYasha fan forums and websites.,would you like to know more about the inuyasha illustrator and writer,similar_yes_no,"Yes, that would be great.","[{'question': 'are you interested in inuyasha wiki activity', 'answer': 'yes am interested in inuyasha wiki activity'}]",maybe can you just tell me how they it works for now
12,how to hire disc jockey,F0088,What jobs are available for disc jockeys?,do you need to book a dj for an event,repeated,"No, I'm interested in having a career as a DJ.","[{'question': 'do you need to book a dj for an event', 'answer': 'no i want to become one'}]",no
96,tell me about rice?,F1056,What is the nutritional value of white rice?,do you want to know the country where rice was created,similar_yes_no,"no, i want to know the nutritional value.","[{'question': 'are you looking for a specific type of rice', 'answer': 'yes white rice'}]",no i would like demographic information
2,Find information on French Lick Resort and Casino.,F0409,Are there discounted packages for staying at French Lick Resort and Casino?,would you like to see resorts and casinos in the french lick area,similar_no_no,"No, I want to know if there are discounted packages available if I stay at the French Lick Resort and Casino.","[{'question': 'would you like to be hired by french lick casino and resort', 'answer': 'no i want to see what kind of discounted packages there are at the french lick resort and casino'}]",no i want to find a streetlevel map of hoboken
4,How to change the toilet in the house,F0812,Where can I buy parts for American Standard toilets?,are you looking for toilet cleaners,similar_yes_no,"No, I look for stores that have parts of toilets","[{'question': 'are you looking for specific products related to toilets', 'answer': 'yes i want a list of parts stores'}]",no i would like to know more about the land rover suv
134,Tell me about electronic skeet shoot.,F0141,retailers selling electronic skeet shooting games with price information,do you want to know what electronic skeet shoot is,repeated,no i want to know which retailers sell electronic skeet shooting games,"[{'question': 'do you want to know what electronic skeet shoot is', 'answer': 'no i want to look at retailers selling electronic skeet shooting games'}]",yes i am looking for pictures of horse hooves
115,Tell me about the pacific northwest laboratory.,F0070,Who operates (manages) PNL?,are you looking for a specific web site,similar_no_no,Pnl website,"[{'question': 'are you looking for a specific representative in relation to the company', 'answer': 'no i am trying to determine who runs the pacific northwest lab'}]",i am interested in the television show star trek voyager
90,tell me about mgb,F1034,Find information on mini gastric bypass surgery.,are you looking for what mgb stands for,similar_yes_no,no i want to know more about mini gastric bypass surgery,"[{'question': 'are you looking for more information about mgb', 'answer': 'yes'}]",no i want to know how they live in india
69,Find sewing instructions for me,F0941,Find helpful sewing tips for beginners.,would you like a book about sewing,similar_no_no,"no, just give me tips for beginners","[{'question': 'would you like to know how to sew on a button', 'answer': 'no i want helpful hints for sewing beginners'}]",no i want an online list of computer programming tutorials
185,How do I get my free annual credit report?,F0359,How is a credit score determined?,are you interested in learning how to read your credit report,repeated,Yeah that would be nice but I also need helping with figuring out the factors that determine it.,"[{'question': 'are you interested in learning how to read your credit report', 'answer': 'partially but can you also explain how it is determined'}]",i want to find about about the migration patterns of the bluethroated hummingbird wherever they are
1,Tell me about Obama family tree.,F0002,Where did Barack Obama's parents and grandparents come from?,are you interested in seeing barack obamas family,similar_yes_no,"Yes, I want more information about them","[{'question': 'would you like to know about obamas ancestors', 'answer': 'yes particualarly information about his parents and grandparents'}]",yes
183,Tell me about kansas city mo,F0350,"What casinos are in Kansas City, Missouri?",would you like to directions to kansas city,repeated,I want to know about the casinos there.,"[{'question': 'would you like to directions to kansas city', 'answer': 'no'}]",no i want flight information not ammenity information
86,tell me about bart sf,F1009,Find maps of the BART system.,are you looking for bart travel schedules,similar_no_no,Not travel schedules. I just want to see the maps.,"[{'question': 'are you looking for contact info in relation to bart sf', 'answer': 'no i am interested in bart system maps'}]",i just need the general history of life and culture
239,Let's see frank lloyd wright biography,F0553,Find biographical information for Frank Lloyd Wright.,would you like a list of the best biographies for frank lloyd wright,similar_yes_no,Not really. I just want to know his biological information.,"[{'question': 'would you like to read some of frank lloyd wrights writings', 'answer': 'yes writings about his personal life'}]",no i want a map of it
33,Find information about elliptical trainer,F0785,What are the benefits of an elliptical trainer compared to other fitness machines?,do you want more information about the benefits of an elliptical trainer,repeated,"Yes, in comparison to other machines.","[{'question': 'do you want more information about the benefits of an elliptical trainer', 'answer': 'yes i would like to know more'}]",i dont know
16,I'm looking for information about game and fish in Arizona.,F0238,Take me to the Arizona Game and Fish Department homepage.,do you want to get a hunting or fishing license in arizona,similar_no_no,"I am not sure, but I would like to go to the homepage.","[{'question': 'would you like the arizona state fish and game comissions contact information', 'answer': 'no i want to go to the arizona state fish and game comissions homepage'}]",yes
151,What is a 403b?,F0201,What is a 403b plan?,would you like to know more about a 403b retirement account,repeated,"Yes, I would like all the details and pricing for the 403b plan.","[{'question': 'would you like to know more about a 403b retirement account', 'answer': 'yes i want to know what the plan is'}]",i dont know
40,what are the popular jobs in Michigan,F0816,What jobs are available in Michigan?,can i take you to the resource page at the michworks website,similar_no_no,"Yes, that sounds like a good resource to start.","[{'question': 'do you need need information related to unemployed services in michigan', 'answer': 'no just the available jobs'}]",only information on nanotechnological
173,Find information on hip fractures,F0305,Find information on hip fractures in the elderly.,were you looking for the causes of hip fractures,repeated,"Yes, specifically what causes hip factures in the elderly.","[{'question': 'were you looking for the causes of hip fractures', 'answer': 'i dont know if i am looking for the cause of hip fractures i am looking for general information'}]",no i am looking for general information about cass county missouri
151,What is a 403b?,F0203,What are the rules for a 403b retirement plan?,would you like to see alternative retirement accounts,similar_yes_no,"No, I want to see them for the 403b.","[{'question': 'are you looking for withdrawal rules for 403b plan', 'answer': 'yes and other relevant rules'}]",yes and specifically the spacecraft and missions
21,Tell me information about Volvo.,F0459,Find a Volvo dealer.,are you interested in who is the ceo,similar_no_no,"No, I would like to find a Volvo car dealership.","[{'question': 'are you asking what year the company originated', 'answer': 'no i am just looking for a dealer'}]",no i want to find reports of problems with windows defender
94,Give me information about Titan.,F1051,"Find information about Saturn's moon, Titan.",are you interested in a specific titan,repeated,"No, I'm interested in Satur's moon, Titan.","[{'question': 'are you interested in a specific titan', 'answer': 'yes i am specifically interested in saturns moon'}]",im trying to get a road map of brazil
144,where can I buy a trombone?,F0176,good places to sell a used trombone,are you interested in the price range for trombones,similar_yes_no,No I just want to know where to sell one.,"[{'question': 'are you interested in selling a trombone you own', 'answer': 'yes'}]",no i am interested in whether they can prediect cervical cancer
138,I'm looking for information on jax chemical company,F0155,Who are retailers that sell Jax Chemical Company's Green Patina solution?,do you need contact information,repeated,Yes.,"[{'question': 'do you need contact information', 'answer': 'no i need to know which retailers sell their jax chemical companies green patrina solution'}]",if it is canadian then yes irregardless im looking at ways people honour poem in your pocket day
39,Give me information about Disneyland hotel.,F0807,Find information on package deals from hotels near Disneyland.,do you want the address,similar_yes_no,"Not really, I want to know more general information about package deals.","[{'question': 'do you want to know how much it costs to stay here', 'answer': 'yes and information on package deals'}]",no i am looking for the history of hoboken
177,what is the best long term care insurance,F0319,What are the different types of long term care insurance policies?,do you plan to sign up for coverage online,similar_no_no,"That's not  important, I want info on the different types of policies.","[{'question': 'would you like to buy a book on the best types of best long term insurances and learn more about it', 'answer': 'no what are the different types of long term care insurance policies'}]",yes i want to know information about horses hooves and how to care for them
99,Tell me more about satilies,F1065,Find background information about man-made satellites.,do you want to know about natural or artificial satellites,repeated,"I want to know about man-made, artificial satellites.","[{'question': 'do you want to know about natural or artificial satellites', 'answer': 'i am interested on information about manmade satellites'}]",no im looking for reviews
159,Find information on Porterville.,F0234,"What colleges or post-secondary institutions are in Porterville, CA?",are you looking to move here,similar_yes_no,No just the colleges located there.,"[{'question': 'are you looking for a specific place here', 'answer': 'yes colleges and postsecondary institutions'}]",i am interested in learning more about the disease itself rather than someone with the disease
93,Information about raffles,F1045,"Find information on organizing a raffle, for example for a charity or school.",are you interested in raffles tv series,repeated,"no, setting up raffles.","[{'question': 'are you interested in raffles tv series', 'answer': 'no'}]",i would like to know how much i have left on my card
94,Give me information about Titan.,F1052,Find the homepage of the Tennessee Titans.,are you referring to the watch brand,similar_no_no,"No, I'm referring to the NFL Football team the Tennessee Titans.","[{'question': 'are you referring to titan the moon of saturn', 'answer': 'no i am referring to the ternnessee titians team'}]",i would like to know how life is in general and its culture
153,Tell me about Pocono,F0210,Find general information on tourist activities in Pennsylvania's Pocono Mountains.,do you want to know the latest weather updates for pocono mountains,similar_yes_no,Yes I do,"[{'question': 'are you referring to pocono mountains', 'answer': 'yes i am'}]",no i am looking for the hompage for starbucks
21,Tell me information about Volvo.,F0458,Where can I find Volvo semi trucks for sale (new or used)?,would you like to know what their rating is compare to other car companies,similar_no_no,"No, I would like to see their semi trucks for sale.","[{'question': 'which part of volvo are you interested in', 'answer': 'no specific part'}]",information for bryant park and any events in new york city
30,Find me information about diabetes education,F0771,I'm looking for nutrition and diet information for diabetics.,do you want to find some resoutces,repeated,"Yes, focused on diets for diabetics","[{'question': 'do you want to find some resoutces', 'answer': 'yes i would like resources for nutrition and diet information for diabetics'}]",no i want to find guides and tips
93,Information about raffles,F1046,Find the homepage of the Raffles hotel in Dubai.,are you interested in the movie raffles,similar_no_no,Find the home  page of Raffles hotel in Dubai.,"[{'question': 'would you like to know more about sir stamford raffles', 'answer': 'no i am looking for a raffles page'}]",no i want the website for the learning programs by the same name
56,tell me about uss yorktown charleston SC,F0885,Find historical information about the USS Yorktown aircraft carriers used during World War 2.,what type of activity are you looking for,repeated,I want to know about the aircraft carriers used during that time.,"[{'question': 'what type of activity are you looking for', 'answer': 'information about the uss yorktown'}]",no
181,I’m interested in old coins,F0340,What is a good way to begin collecting old coins?,is there a coin dealer near you,similar_yes_no,"I don't know, but how to do I collect old coins?","[{'question': 'do you want to buy old coins', 'answer': 'yes i want to find out what is the best way to begin an old coin collection'}]",i am intrested in the real estate
240,Tell me more about us presidents,F0558,Find a list of the full names of US presidents.,do you want to know what middle name is the most common for presidents,similar_no_no,"No, I want a list of all the full names of former US presidents.","[{'question': 'are you looking for the middle names of the early presidents', 'answer': 'no i want to know what the full name of the presidents in the us'}]",no i am looking for the history of hoboken
55,tell me about iron,F0882,Find information about the element iron (Fe).,are you looking for irons melting point,repeated,"No, I want information of the elemnt Iron.","[{'question': 'are you looking for irons melting point', 'answer': 'yes i am looking for general information about iron'}]",no im looking to buy replacement parts
39,Give me information about Disneyland hotel.,F0808,Find reviews of Disneyland hotels.,do you want to know how much it costs to stay here,similar_yes_no,"no, i just need reviews of the disneyland hotel","[{'question': 'are you looking for a hotel inside disneyland', 'answer': 'yes i am looking for a place to stay in disneyland'}]",i need the address for the ontario canada airport
57,tell me about ct jobs,F0887,Find sites for finding a job in Connecticut.,which part of connecticut are you interested in,similar_no_no,I'm interested in all of Connecticut.,"[{'question': 'what salary range are you looking for', 'answer': 'none im looking for job search web sites'}]",no id like to know about indian tribes that lived in adobe houses
173,Find information on hip fractures,F0307,How many hip fractures occur annually in the US?,do you want to know what the symptoms of a hip fracture are,repeated,How many hip fractures occur annually in the US?,"[{'question': 'do you want to know what the symptoms of a hip fracture are', 'answer': 'no i want to know how many hip fractures occur in the us a year'}]",no im looking for more quotes like it
98,Find me information on sat,F1061,Find general information about the SATs.,are you referring to saturday or the verb,similar_yes_no,i just want general information about the sats,"[{'question': 'are you looking for the nearest sat testing location', 'answer': 'yes but i would also like to know general information about the test'}]",yes i would like more information about expats living in india
90,tell me about mgb,F1033,Find sites for MGB car owners and enthusiasts.,are you looking for mini gastric bypass surgery,similar_no_no,No I want info on MGB for car people.,"[{'question': 'are you interested in buying or selling an mgb', 'answer': 'no i am looking for sites for mgb car owners and enthusiasts'}]",yes that would be helpful information
102,What is Fickle Creek Farm,F0014,Find general information about Fickle Creek Farm in North Carolina,are you looking for information about staying at fickle creek farm,repeated,I want information about the farm in general.,"[{'question': 'are you looking for information about staying at fickle creek farm', 'answer': 'no i am looking for more general information'}]",no i want information on where the stores are located
77,Information about bobcat,F0973,Find attachments for bobcat tractors.,would you like to know the habitat of the bobcat,similar_yes_no,"No, I want to see the attachments for the bobcat tractors.","[{'question': 'are you looking for a specific tractor model', 'answer': 'yes the bobcat model'}]",no what careers are for computer programmers
189,Find information about the gs pay rate,F0370,Find the General Schedule pay tables.,do you need a gs pay calculator,repeated,"no, just the gs pay tables","[{'question': 'do you need a gs pay calculator', 'answer': 'no i want to see the gs pay tables'}]",i want to see the obituaries
92,Find information about the wall,F1040,"Find information about the Vietnam Veterans Memorial in Washington, DC.",are you referring to the nbc television show,similar_no_no,"No I'm referring to the Vietnam Veterans Memorial in Waschinton, DC.","[{'question': 'are you looking for a specific web site', 'answer': 'no any web site about the vietnam veterans memorial would be good'}]",i dont know
53,discovery channel store,F0870,Find Discovery Channel store locations.,are you looking for a mythbusters product,similar_yes_no,"no, where are discovery channel stores located?","[{'question': 'shall i open discovery channel store homepage', 'answer': 'yes'}]",no i am looking for a map of street level hoboken new jersey
64,I'd like to learn about moths,F0918,Find pictures of moths.,are you interested in moth biology,repeated,I am interested in pictures of moths in general.,"[{'question': 'are you interested in moth biology', 'answer': 'no i am looking for pictures of moths'}]",i want the demographic information on cass county mo
187,Tell me about vanuatu,F0364,I need travel and tourism information for Vanuatu.,are you interested in the location of vanuatu,similar_yes_no,"Yes, what are the must see places there","[{'question': 'do you want a map', 'answer': 'yes along with other tourist information like beaches and hotels'}]",no i would like specific details on the migration period of blue throated hummingbirds
28,I'm interested in InuYasha,F0697,I'm looking for pictures and wallpaper images from InuYasha.,how would you like to watch inuyasha episodes,similar_no_no,"No, I want an InuYasha wallpaper.","[{'question': 'are you interested in a specific season of inuyasha', 'answer': 'no im looking for wallpapers of inuyasha not seasons'}]",i need facility information on the ontario ca airport
59,how to build a fence?,F0899,Where can I buy materials for building a fence?,are you looking for instructions to build a fence,repeated,"no, i want to know where i can get materials for building a fence.","[{'question': 'are you looking for instructions to build a fence', 'answer': 'no i am looking for places to buy materials to build a fence'}]",yes id like more information on the show
15,Give me espn sports information.,F0196,I'm looking for information on fantasy football leagues.,do you want to know what channel espn is,similar_no_no,"no, i just need general information about fantasy football leagues","[{'question': 'do you want to know who owns espn', 'answer': 'no i only want information on fantasy football leagues'}]",this is not related to my search
87,who invented music,F1011,Find information on the history and development of music.,do you want to know the first song ever recorded,similar_yes_no,"Sure, that is one thing.","[{'question': 'would you like to know about inventions related to music', 'answer': 'yes and other history'}]",yes
86,tell me about bart sf,F1009,Find maps of the BART system.,for what route are you seeking information,repeated,"No specific route, just an overall map of the entire system.","[{'question': 'for what route are you seeking information', 'answer': 'i just want general map information'}]",i would like to know how it could be treated
11,How to prepare for the GMAT?,F0046,I'd like to find some tips to help me do well on the GMAT.,do you want to know the cost of a gmat prep class,similar_no_no,I am not interested in this topic.,"[{'question': 'would you like to know what distinguishes gmat from gre', 'answer': 'no i would like tips on helping me do well on the gmat'}]",no i would like specific details on the migration period of blue throated hummingbirds
42,I’m looking for the music man.,F0824,Find recordings of songs from The Music Man.,do you want to know the actors in the music man,similar_yes_no,"No, I want to hear songs from The Music Man.","[{'question': 'are you trying to find videos about the music man', 'answer': 'yes but i only want videos with songs'}]",no i am looking for information about degree programs
61,I’m looking for information on worm,F0908,Find information about worms in nature.,are you interested in knowing more about a computer worm,repeated,"no, real worms.","[{'question': 'are you interested in knowing more about a computer worm', 'answer': 'no real worms'}]",yes im referring this game and is it possible to play online
296,I'm looking for information on recycling lead acid batteries,F0753,Where can I recycle lead acid batteries?,are you interested in the recycling process for lead acid batteries,similar_no_no,"no, i just want to know where i can recycle them","[{'question': 'what was the lead acid battery you want to recycle used for', 'answer': 'no information given'}]",no tell me about horse shoeing and horse shoe problems
31,Find information about atari,F0774,I want to read about the history of the Atari 2600 and other Atari game consoles.,are you interested in buying a new atari game console,similar_yes_no,"No, I am interested in the history of it.","[{'question': 'are you interested in the history of atari', 'answer': 'yes'}]",no i am needing it for the budget planning from the start
66,I need information on income tax return online,F0928,Find a site where I can fill out my Federal income tax return online.,how did you file your previous year taxes,repeated,I used Turbotax to complete my taxes last year.,"[{'question': 'how did you file your previous year taxes', 'answer': 'on paper'}]",yes and other information
28,I'm interested in InuYasha,F0700,I'm looking for InuYasha fan forums and websites.,would you like to know more about the inuyasha illustrator and writer,similar_yes_no,more a fan base,"[{'question': 'are you looking for specific fanrelated information', 'answer': 'yes im looking for fan forums and websites'}]",no i am interested in learning about computer memory
58,Find information about penguins.,F0895,"Find pictures of the penguins from the animated movie, ""Madagascar"".",would you like to buy a book about this topic,similar_no_no,"No just show me pictures of  the penguins from the movie ""Madagascar"".","[{'question': 'do you want to watch funny penguin videos', 'answer': 'no i want to see images of penguins'}]",no i am looking for information on the mathematician euclid
160,What are the best recepies for grilling,F0247,Find information on gas barbecue grills and cooking on a gas grill.,do you want to see cookbooks for grilling,repeated,"as I mentioned before, I want general info.","[{'question': 'do you want to see cookbooks for grilling', 'answer': 'no i would like general information on gas grills and how to cook on a gas grill'}]",no i am interested in finding out the number of times atypical squamous cells predict cervical cancer
141,How to register dmv in va?,F0168,Where are offices of the Virginia Department of Motor Vehicles located and what are their hours of operation?,do you want a list of departments within the va dmv registration,similar_yes_no,"yes, with priority to those that have their hours of operation","[{'question': 'would you like directions to the va dmv registration', 'answer': 'yes also what hours ar they opn'}]",no i need information on shoeing horses and horseshoe problems
60,Tell me about Bellevue.,F0904,Find the homepage of Bellevue University.,do you want to know about the nearest town named bellevue,similar_no_no,"No, I want to know more about Bellevue University.","[{'question': 'are you looking for things to do in bellevue', 'answer': 'no i want to find information about the college'}]",no
136,Tell me about american military university.,F0147,reviews and commentary on the quality of education received by students at American Military University,would you be interested in learning more about the history of the american military university,repeated,"No, I want to learn the opinions of people about it from recent times.","[{'question': 'would you be interested in learning more about the history of the american military university', 'answer': 'no i want to know more about what people say about the university and its reviews'}]",no not the scientist i need the webpage for euclid chemical company
72,Find information about the sun.,F0954,"Find the homepage for the U.K. newspaper, The Sun.",are you looking for the news paper the sun,similar_no_yes,"Yes, please show me their homepage.","[{'question': 'are you interested in the suns life cycle', 'answer': 'no i want to find the homepage of the newspaper'}]",none i just need ontario cas airport address
58,Find information about penguins.,F0892,Find Pittsburgh Penguins merchandise such as hockey jerseys.,are you interested in a specific type of penguin,similar_no_yes,Yes I need Pittsburgh Penguins hockey jerseys,"[{'question': 'would you like to know the penguins schedule', 'answer': 'no i am interested in clothing items only'}]",yes that would be helpful
11,How to prepare for the GMAT?,F0045,I'm looking for some free sample GMAT exams to practice on.,are you looking for gmat prep classes near you,repeated,Just like what I said before.,"[{'question': 'are you looking for gmat prep classes near you', 'answer': 'yes i am looking for gmat prep classes near my current location'}]",yes
28,I'm interested in InuYasha,F0701,Find music from the InuYasha television series.,are you interested in the list of inuyasha characters,similar_no_no,i need music from the inuyasha tv series,"[{'question': 'would you like to see inuyasha manga', 'answer': 'now i want music from the tv series'}]",tell me about the problems that all models of ford edge have ever had
94,Give me information about Titan.,F1050,Find the homepage for Titan motorcycles.,are you interested in a specific web page,similar_yes_yes,"Yes, whatever leads me to possibly purchasing a Titan.","[{'question': 'are you interested in a specific titan', 'answer': 'yes titan motorcycles'}]",yes what tourist attractions are in cass county mo
5,Find information about Mitchell College.,F0854,Find information on admissions to Mitchell College. How do I become a student there?,should i request an application to mitchell college,similar_no_yes,"Yes, I think that would be nice.","[{'question': 'what state is mitchell college in', 'answer': 'i dont know but can you find it and tell me what i have to do to enroll there'}]",no i want to know the 2008 budget for cass county mo
197,tell me about idaho state flower,F0398,What is the state flower of Idaho?,would you like to know how big they grow,similar_no_no,i just want to know what the state flower is,"[{'question': 'are you interested in where they grow', 'answer': 'no i want the name of the state flower of idaho'}]",no i want examples of poems written for that day
162,Tell me more about dnr,F0252,"What are ""do not resuscitate"" orders and how do you get one in place?",do you mean do not resuscitate,similar_no_yes,yes and i want to know how to get a dnr implemented.,"[{'question': 'do you want to know the legality of dnr', 'answer': 'no i want to know how i implement them'}]",only if the app contains obitaries
194,Tell me about designer dog breeds.,F0387,What breeds of small or toy dog hybrids are there?,do you want to know what are cosidered designer dog breeds,similar_yes_yes,"Yes and everything concerning the diog breed,","[{'question': 'do you want to know unusual designer dog breeds', 'answer': 'yes i want to know unusual designer dog breeds'}]",i am looking for images or a diagram of a horse hoof
70,to be or not to be that is the question,F0947,Find famous quotes from Shakespeare's plays.,are you referring to shakespear,similar_no_yes,"No, I am referring to Shakespeare.","[{'question': 'do you want to know the meaning of the quote', 'answer': 'no i want to know all famous quotes from shakespeares plays'}]",yes
99,Tell me more about satilies,F1069,Find providers of satellite internet service.,are you referring to satellite imagery on google maps,similar_no_no,"No, I am looking for internet providers that use satellite.","[{'question': 'do you want to figure out the benefits of satellite tv over cable tv', 'answer': 'no i need satellite internet providers'}]",yes the one for the city of hoboken nj
141,How to register dmv in va?,F0169,home page of the Virginia Department of Motor Vehicles,are you looking for a specific web page,similar_yes_yes,"Yes, I am looking for the homepage of the Virginia Department of Motor Vehicles.","[{'question': 'are you searching for required documentation for vehicle registration', 'answer': 'yes'}]",i would like to know famous quotes from the declaration of indepence
15,Give me espn sports information.,F0195,I'm looking for information on NASCAR races.,do you want to know when espn started,similar_no_no,"No, I want information on Nascar races.","[{'question': 'do you wnat sports scores', 'answer': 'no i am looking for general information on nascar races'}]",no i want to know what types of panels exist
29,Tell me about ps 2 games?,F0733,What are the specifications of the PlayStation 2 console?,would you like to know more about ps2 console design,similar_no_yes,"no, i just want information about the ps2 specifications","[{'question': 'are you looking for ps 2 games prices', 'answer': 'no i need the specifications for the ps 2 gaming console'}]",no
32,I'm looking for information on web design and hosting.,F0781,"Find reviews of web hosting services, geared towards small business needs.",are you interested in paid services,similar_yes_yes,"Sure, as long as it has reviews.","[{'question': 'would you like to see reviews for website hosting and design companies', 'answer': 'yes i am looking for reviews'}]",no i want information on disposing of dog waste
30,Find me information about diabetes education,F0772,How can I become a diabetes educator?,are you wanting to find a class on the education of the disease of diabetes,similar_yes_yes,Yes that's what I'm looking for.,"[{'question': 'do you want to find some resoutces', 'answer': 'yes if they can tell me how to become a diabetes educator'}]",no i need to a list of the real estate listings for the hoboken nj area
94,Give me information about Titan.,F1052,Find the homepage of the Tennessee Titans.,are you interested in a specific web page,similar_no_yes,"Ya , I am very interested for that","[{'question': 'are you referring to the monster from the final fantasy series', 'answer': 'no i am referring to the nfl team the tennessee titans'}]",its a hobby store
6,Tell me more on Kansas city railroad,F0900,"Find information on KCS Energy, Inc., and their merger with Petrohawk Energy Corporation.",do you want to know about kennycaffey syndorme,similar_no_no,No I want to know about KCS energy and their merger.,"[{'question': 'are you looking for the kcs academy', 'answer': 'no im looking for information on kcs energy'}]",no i just need some general historical information about the island its people
62,Tell me about texas border patrol.,F0912,How do I get a job with the U.S. Border Patrol in Texas?,do you want to know how to become one,similar_no_yes,Yes.,"[{'question': 'do you want to apply for a job here', 'answer': 'no but i am looking for employment within a specific area'}]",no i am interested in seeing an image of the declaration of independence at the national archives
171,Tell me about ron howard.,F0300,"Who are Ron Howard's family members: parents, wife, any children?",are you looking for ron howard biographies,similar_yes_yes,"Specifically, I want to know about his family, including his kids and spouse.","[{'question': 'do you want to know how old ron howard is', 'answer': 'yes i would love to know how old ron howard is'}]",defender marine supplies
87,who invented music,F1012,Find a history of classical music.,is there any specific music genre you are interested in,similar_no_yes,I am interested in classical music,"[{'question': 'do you wish to know how music videos started', 'answer': 'no i want to know about the history of classical music'}]",no i want a list of hobby stores that carry train sets
77,Information about bobcat,F0971,Find dealers that sell or rent Bobcat tractors and construction equipment.,would you like to know the location of the headquarters of the company bobcat,similar_no_no,No just places that sell or rent them.,"[{'question': 'are you interested in the evolution of bobcats', 'answer': 'no im interested in selling or renting bobcat tractors and equipment'}]",im looking for a black white outline map that a child could color
33,Find information about elliptical trainer,F0783,I'm looking for reviews of elliptical machines.,would you like to see reviews on elliptical trainers,similar_yes_yes,"yes, i would","[{'question': 'are you interested in different brands of elliptical trainer', 'answer': 'yes and also reviews of each brand'}]",no i am interested in what the computer science program entails to complete requirements description of the courses and knowledge taught
39,Give me information about Disneyland hotel.,F0808,Find reviews of Disneyland hotels.,are you looking for a hotel inside disneyland,similar_no_yes,"yes, i need reviews for the disneyland hotel.","[{'question': 'do you want a phone number to call', 'answer': 'no i would like a link to a website where i can see reviews about disneyland hotels'}]",no tell me about horse shoeing and horse shoe problems
147,tell me about tangible personal property tax,F0184,When is the tangible personal property tax due?,are you reffering to the federal or state tax,similar_no_no,"I do not know, I am referring to tangible property tax.","[{'question': 'what is theh tax rate for the country youre in', 'answer': 'i do not know i need to know when the tangible personal property tax is due'}]",yes specifically for poem in your pocket day
22,I'm looking for information on Rick Warren.,F0499,I'm looking for background and biographical information on Rick Warren.,do you want to know how old rick warren is,similar_no_yes,just give me general biographical information,"[{'question': 'do you need any specific information on obama inauguration', 'answer': 'no i want information on rick warren including any backgound or biographical information'}]",yes
146,What can I do in sherwood regional library,F0179,What services are provided by the Sherwood Regional Library?,would you like the see the calendar of events,similar_no_no,"No, I am asking which services are available.","[{'question': 'are you looking to reserve a space at the sherwood regional library', 'answer': 'not necessarily i am interested in all of the activities classes and services that occur through or at sherwood regional library'}]",no i just want to go to the starbucks homepage
52,Tell me about avp,F0863,"Go to the homepage for the AVP, sponsor of professional beach volleyball events.",are you looking for avp beach volleyball,similar_yes_yes,Yes.,"[{'question': 'are you referring to a specific company', 'answer': 'yes the homepage of avp'}]",no i am looking for information about human memory
185,How do I get my free annual credit report?,F0356,How do I get my free annual credit report?,wou you like to know more about 3in1 credit reports,similar_no_yes,Just like i said before.,"[{'question': 'do you want information on how to keep your credit report good', 'answer': 'no i want to know how to get a free credit report'}]",no i am looking for bars and nightclubs in hoboken
2,Find information on French Lick Resort and Casino.,F0408,What jobs are available at French Lick Casino and Resort?,are you looking for a particular casino in french lick,similar_yes_yes,"yes, jobs at french lick resort and casino.","[{'question': 'would you like to be hired by french lick casino and resort', 'answer': 'yes what are the available jobs there'}]",no im looking for user reports about windows defender
138,I'm looking for information on jax chemical company,F0154,What type of surface treatment products does Jax Chemical Company manufacture?,are you referring to the nbc television show,off_topic,No. What surface treatment products does Jax Chemical Company make?,"[{'question': 'do you need info on jax chemical company', 'answer': 'yes i need information on their products'}]",no i just want to know the problems with the car
53,discovery channel store,F0870,Find Discovery Channel store locations.,are you looking for a specific web site,off_topic,"Yes, the discovery channel store website.","[{'question': 'shall i open discovery channel store homepage', 'answer': 'yes'}]",i want to know what hotels are near
41,Looking for information about the Orange County Convention Center,F0820,How do I reserve the Orange County Convention Center for an event?,are you looking for the convention center in florida,similar_yes_yes,How do i reserve the orange country convention centre for an event?,"[{'question': 'are you planning any events there', 'answer': 'yes i would like information about booking events there'}]",i dont know
22,I'm looking for information on Rick Warren.,F0500,I want to see articles and web pages about the controversy over Rick Warren's invocation at the Obama inauguration.,are you referring to the pastor,similar_no_yes,"Yes, Rick Warren the pastor.","[{'question': 'are you looking for the age of rick warren', 'answer': 'no i just want to read about the controversy involving warren and obamas inauguration'}]",i dont know
31,Find information about atari,F0776,Find information about classic Atari games.,would you like to see a list of atari games,similar_yes_yes,Yes but for the classic Atari.,"[{'question': 'are you interested in atari 2600', 'answer': 'yes if it is classic'}]",yes the racing schedule
59,how to build a fence?,F0898,What materials are best for building fences?,are you looking for black history figures,off_topic,"no, i am looking for information about building fences.","[{'question': 'are you using this around the yard', 'answer': 'maybe what are the best materials for buiding fences'}]",no i want to know how does someone build an adobe house
160,What are the best recepies for grilling,F0246,Find the Grilling Magazine website.,are you looking for the magazine the grilling,similar_no_yes,"No, I am looking for the main website for the grilling magazine.","[{'question': 'are you interested in a recipe for grilled chicken', 'answer': 'no show me the grilling magazine website'}]",no i am looking for a map of political jurisdictions in brazil not a transportation map
184,I’m interested in civil right movement,F0355,What is the history of the Little Rock nine?,do you want to check out a certain book or see if it is available,off_topic,"Yes, if it is about the Little Rock nine.","[{'question': 'do you want to know who started the movement', 'answer': 'no i want to know more about the little rock nine'}]",i am curious about the budget for cass county mo
28,I'm interested in InuYasha,F0698,Find InuYasha anime episodes for download.,would you like to watch an inuyasha movie,similar_yes_yes,Yes if I can download them.,"[{'question': 'are you interested in a specific season of inuyasha', 'answer': 'yes i want to download some episodes'}]",no i want a picture of the document the declaration of independence
158,How should I use the septic system design,F0232,I need a septic system contractor.,are you trying to find a contractor,similar_no_yes,Yes for septic systems.,"[{'question': 'are you interested in a pressure distributon design 2 feet of absorbant soil', 'answer': 'no what i am looking for are contractors that maintain and install septic systems'}]",yes what type of services do they offer there
198,Tell me more about indiana state fairgrounds.,F0402,Find driving directions to the Indiana State Fairgrounds.,do you want to attend the indiana state fair,similar_yes_yes,I just want directions for getting to the fairgrounds by car.,"[{'question': 'would you like to know where indiana state fairgrounds is on a map', 'answer': 'yes i would appreciate that information'}]",yes i need to find poems related to poem in your pocket day
199,Tell me about fybromyalgia,F0407,What support groups are there for fybromyalgia suffers?,would you like help searching for work in michigan,off_topic,"No, I am looking for support groups for fibromyalgia sufferers.","[{'question': 'what type of fibromyalgia statistics are you looking for', 'answer': 'i am looking for fibromyalgia support groups'}]",no i need to know if i can buy dog clean up bags online
134,Tell me about electronic skeet shoot.,F0141,retailers selling electronic skeet shooting games with price information,would you like to see the retailers selling it,similar_no_yes,"Yes, along with details about what they charge.","[{'question': 'would you like to know different types of it', 'answer': 'no i would like to find retailers and pricing information for electronic skeet shooting games'}]",no a streetlevel view of hoboken
73,Tell me about Neil Young.,F0957,Find biographical information about Neil Young.,do you want his biography,similar_yes_yes,"Yes, that it correct.","[{'question': 'are you interested in neil youngs history', 'answer': 'yes'}]",no i am not interested in nutritional information
211,What is Madagascar known for?,F0467,What is Madagascar known for?,are you interested in where the bowflex power pro is produced,off_topic,"no, i want to know what madagascar is famous for","[{'question': 'would you like to know what plants are native to madagascar', 'answer': 'no i need to know what the island is known for'}]",no
156,I need information about the University of Phoenix.,F0224,Find homepages of faculty members at the University of Phoenix.,do you need the website for the university of phoenix,similar_no_yes,"No, I need a faculty page.","[{'question': 'are you interested in comparing university of phoenix with other universities in any specific aspect', 'answer': 'no i want to know about the faculty'}]",i woukd like to know the cost and guidelines of a wedding
122,Tell me more about Culpeper National Cemetry,F0098,Where is the Culpeper National Cemetery located?,would you like to know the way to culpeper national cemetary,similar_yes_yes,Sure. Please include the address.,"[{'question': 'do you need the address of culpeper national cemetery', 'answer': 'yes'}]",i want general information on the artwork used on rock music album covers
48,tell me about wilson antenna,F0844,What kinds of CB antennas does Wilson Antenna sell?,would you like information on filing income taxes,off_topic,"No, tell me the kind of CB antennas Wilson Antenna sells.","[{'question': 'would you like to know about where to purchase a wilson antenna', 'answer': 'no i want to know what kind of cb antennas they sell'}]",no a simply map that a child could color
168,What are the causes of lipoma tumors,F0282,What are the treatments for malignant lipolysis?,do you need treatment information for lipoma,similar_no_yes,What are the treatments for malignant lipolysis?,"[{'question': 'are you looking for the definition to lipoma', 'answer': 'no i am looking for treatments for malignant lipolysis'}]",yes specifically how squamous cells predict it
182,How can I quick smoking,F0343,What are the ways you can quit smoking?,are you looking for information on how to quit smoking,similar_yes_yes,"Yes, I am. I want to quit smoking.","[{'question': 'are you wondering how other people have quit smoking', 'answer': 'yes'}]",yes but also tell me general information about it
170,Tell me about scooters.,F0294,Find the homepage of Hoveround scooters.,do you want to know how to use it,off_topic,"no, give me the homepage of Hoveround scooters.","[{'question': 'would you like to purchase one or rent it', 'answer': 'just looking for the homepage right now'}]",yes with roads
130,What are characteristics of Uranus,F0128,"What do we know about Uranus, versus what open questions are there about the planet?",do you want to know how old it is estimated to be,similar_yes_yes,"Yes, I would like to know what we know for certain about the planet.","[{'question': 'are you wondering the size of uranus', 'answer': 'yes i want to know about uranus'}]",no i am not
183,Tell me about kansas city mo,F0348,What hotels are near the Kansas City airport?,are you interested in visiting kansas city,similar_no_yes,i just want to know about hotels for now,"[{'question': 'would you like to see a listing for hotels in kansas city', 'answer': 'no i would like to see a listing of hotels that are near the kansas city airport'}]",yes
21,Tell me information about Volvo.,F0459,Find a Volvo dealer.,do you want to purchase an atari game,off_topic,No I want to find a dealer for Volvos.,"[{'question': 'do you need information about a volvo dealership', 'answer': 'yes'}]",no im interest more in information about illinois sales tax and how the rate is levied
76,Find information on raised gardens.,F0969,What kind of wood should be used to build a raised garden bed?,do you want to know how to create a raised garden,similar_no_yes,I would like to know what materials are recommended for a raised garden.,"[{'question': 'do you want to buy a book about raised gardens', 'answer': 'no i just need to know what kind of wood should be used to build a raised garden'}]",no i am interested in arts and crafts
72,Find information about the sun.,F0953,"Find information about the Sun, the star in our Solar System.",do you want to know facts about the sun,similar_yes_yes,"yes, tell me general facts about the sun","[{'question': 'are you looking for a history of solar eclipses', 'answer': 'yes but not specifically only that topic'}]",no i just need to find the hompeage for the city
40,what are the popular jobs in Michigan,F0816,What jobs are available in Michigan?,would you like help searching for work in michigan,similar_no_yes,"Yes, I would like this.","[{'question': 'can i take you to the resource page at the michworks website', 'answer': 'no take me to a site with job listing in michigan'}]",yes i am looking for general information on kiwi fruit
87,who invented music,F1014,Who invented the radio?,are you interested in learning about arkansas,off_topic,"no, i want to know who invented the radio","[{'question': 'do you want the name of one person', 'answer': 'i want the name of the person who invented the radio'}]",news related to pending sale of the rocky mountain news
180,Tell me about hotels in New York.,F0337,"Where are hotels on Long Island, New York?",are you looking for a chain or botique hotel,similar_yes_yes,Either one is fine with me.,"[{'question': 'do you need a map of hotels', 'answer': 'yes id like to see a map of the hotels in long island'}]",actually i would like the history of life and culture in india
127,I'm looking for information on duchess county tourism,F0113,Find the homepage of Dutchess County (NY) Tourism.,would you like information on filing income taxes,off_topic,"No, just the homepage for Dutchess County Tourism.","[{'question': 'what activities in dutchess county were you interested in', 'answer': 'this is not related to my search'}]",yes
109,I'm looking for information about mayo clinic Jacksonville FL,F0043,"Housing information for outpatients of the Mayo Clinic in Jacksonville, FL.",are you looking for outpatient services in mayo clinic,similar_yes_yes,I want to find housing information for outpatients at the Mayo Clinic.,"[{'question': 'would you like to know the address of mayo clinic jacksonville fl', 'answer': 'yes'}]",no im looking for reviews
154,figs,F0215,Find recipes that use figs.,are you interested in recipes you can make with figs fresh or dried,similar_no_yes,"Either one, as long as they're recipes.","[{'question': 'are you interested in the calorie count or other nutrition information for the fruit', 'answer': 'no i am not i want fig recipes'}]",no i want you to find me the sports reporters for the rocky mountain news
47,Tell me more about USA tax for annuity,F0841,What is an indexed annuity? What are their advantages and disadvantages? What kinds of indexed annuities are there?,would you like to know the advantages and disadvantages of a indexed annuity,similar_no_yes,What is an indexed annuity? What are their advantages and disadvantages?,"[{'question': 'do you know what an indexed annuity is', 'answer': 'i do not know what an indexed annuity is i want to find that out as well as the advantages and disadvantages of the different kinds of annuities'}]",no i want to find out just how one can become a consultant on the pampered chef show
162,Tell me more about dnr,F0254,What are the Maryland Department of Natural Resources' regulations for deer hunting?,would you like to know more about hunting rules,similar_yes_yes,"Yes, sepcifically Marylands regulations on deer hunting.","[{'question': 'do you mean the department of natural resources', 'answer': 'yes in maryland for deer hunting'}]",no i would like to go to the homepage for defender marine supplies
98,Find me information on sat,F1062,What are typical and good ranges for SAT scores? What is the average score?,do you want to know who owns the company imclone,off_topic,"No, I want to know what people typically score on the sat exams.","[{'question': 'do you want to take a sat prep class', 'answer': 'no i want to know typical and good ranges of sat scores and what the average score is'}]",yes id like to know who wrote it
16,I'm looking for information about game and fish in Arizona.,F0239,What are the regulations for hunting and fishing in Arizona?,do you want information about the arizona game and fish department,similar_yes_yes,Yes please,"[{'question': 'would you like to see information on fishing in arizona', 'answer': 'yes specifically regulations from arizona fish and wildlife'}]",yes im looking for the homepage
176,Tell me about weather stripping,F0317,What is the best way to seal or weather strip my garage door?,would you like to learn about weather stripping,similar_no_yes,"Yes, for garage doors specifically.","[{'question': 'would you like to know what a weather strip is', 'answer': 'no i want to know how to weather strip my door'}]",yes specifically about working as a computer programmer
155,Find me information about the Last Supper painting.,F0220,What is the significance of da Vinci's interpretation of the Last Supper in Catholicism?,are you looking for things to do around that area,off_topic,No I want info on the painting and what it could mean.,"[{'question': 'are you interested in the history of the last supper painting', 'answer': 'no i would like to know more about the meaning'}]",yes exactly
105,Tell me about sonoma county medical services.,F0026,"I'm looking for the home page of the County Medical Services Program (CMSP) of Sonoma County, California.",do you need any specific information on health insurance,similar_no_yes,Im looking for the home page of the country medical service program.,"[{'question': 'are you looking for specific program information', 'answer': 'no just the front page'}]",no im looking for information on the different programming languages
132,I'm interested in mothers day songs,F0132,lyrics of songs written for Mothers' Day,are you looking for documentaries of people who live with ocd,off_topic,"No, I want to see lyrics from Mothers' Day songs.","[{'question': 'are you interested in remembrance songs', 'answer': 'no i am interested in mothers day songs'}]",no i want locations
87,who invented music,F1012,Find a history of classical music.,are you looking for the history of classical music,similar_yes_yes,"Yes, that is what I want.","[{'question': 'is there any specific music genre you are interested in', 'answer': 'yes classical musics history is what i which to learn about'}]",no i am looking for information on cave paintings in france
23,What is yahoo,F0528,Take me to Yahoo! Finance.,shall i take you to any specific pages of yahoo web site,similar_no_yes,"Yes, the Finance section.","[{'question': 'do you want to access yahoo mail', 'answer': 'no i want to access yahoo finance'}]",no i want to host a show
137,tell me about rock and gem shows,F0150,rock and gem shows that offer lapidary classes,are you interested in the quote from hamlet,off_topic,I'm not interested in a quote from a play.,"[{'question': 'are you interested in finding rock and gem shows near you', 'answer': 'yes'}]",no can you give me some examples of employee performance appraisals
261,Tell me about folk remedies for a sore throat.,F0633,What folk remedies are there for soothing a sore throat?,are you looking for homeopathic remedies for a sore throat,similar_yes_yes,"Yes, please give me the answer now.","[{'question': 'do you want to learn about home health care when you have a sore throat', 'answer': 'yes i want to know what i can use at home to help my sore throat'}]",no just movies about civil war battles
31,Find information about atari,F0777,Find information about Atari arcade games.,are you interested in playing online games,similar_yes_yes,"Yes, I am interested in playing online games, although I am a big fan of the Atari 2600. Some of them are even online now in days","[{'question': 'are you interested in atari 2600', 'answer': 'yes'}]",no i just want to kno its common name
15,Give me espn sports information.,F0194,I'm looking for baseball scores and information on upcoming live broadcast games.,do you wnat sports scores,similar_no_yes,I'm looking for baseball scores and information on upcoming live broadcast games.,"[{'question': 'do you want information about espn sports programming in languages other than english', 'answer': 'no can you just give me baseball scores and tell me about upcoming live broadcast games'}]",yes i need to buy parts
135,Tell me about source of the nile,F0144,information on the feud between Speke and Burton over the discovery of the source of the Nile river,what information do you need about bart sf,off_topic,i want to know why speke and burton had a feud about the nile.,"[{'question': 'do you want to know what country the source is in', 'answer': 'no i want to know about the feud between speke and burton over the discovery'}]",no
228,Tell me more about Hawain volcanos,F0525,I am looking for the history of and a summary of the work performed at the Hawaiian Volcano Observatories.,would you like to know where the observatories are located,similar_yes_yes,Yeah that would be great. Any details about historical information too.,"[{'question': 'are you looking for activity summeries of the volcanoes that the hawaiian volcano observatories is currently watching', 'answer': 'yes and the history'}]",no i need to nutritional information on starbucks products
91,Tell me about er television show.,F1036,Find episodes of ER I can download or watch online.,are you looking for ways to watch er,similar_no_yes,"I am looking for ways to watch the episodes online or download them, yes.","[{'question': 'do you want to know awards er has won', 'answer': 'no i want to watch episodes of the show'}]",i am curious about the budget for cass county mo
211,What is Madagascar known for?,F0467,What is Madagascar known for?,would you like to know what animals are native to madagascar,similar_yes_yes,"Yes, that would be interesting to know.","[{'question': 'are you looking for tourist attractions in madagascar', 'answer': 'yes and id like to know what it is known for'}]",yes that would be great
17,I'm interested in poker tournaments,F0290,I'm looking for a schedule of poker tournaments in Atlantic City.,would you like instructions on how to use a sewing machine,off_topic,"No. I want a schedule of poker tournaments in Atlantic City, NJ.","[{'question': 'where would you like to find poker tournaments', 'answer': 'in atlantic city and their schedules'}]",yes i am specifically looking for the balance on on the card
144,where can I buy a trombone?,F0176,good places to sell a used trombone,are you interested in selling a trombone you own,similar_yes_yes,"Yes, where can I find them?","[{'question': 'would you like to see music stores in your area', 'answer': 'yes i want music stores'}]",no just the address
16,I'm looking for information about game and fish in Arizona.,F0238,Take me to the Arizona Game and Fish Department homepage.,are you looking for a specific web site,similar_no_yes,I am looking for the specific homepage for Arizona's Game and Fish Department.,"[{'question': 'do you want to get a hunting or fishing license in arizona', 'answer': 'no i need the arizona game and fish department homepage'}]",no im looking for information on the kiwi bird
26,How can I lower my heart rate?,F0626,How can I lower my heart rate?,do you need to apply for a federal tax return online,off_topic,"No, I do not.","[{'question': 'are you planning to run or exercise', 'answer': 'no'}]",yes id like more information on the show
122,Tell me more about Culpeper National Cemetry,F0097,What is the history of the Culpeper National Cemetery?,do you want to know the history of culpeper national cemetery,similar_yes_yes,"Yes, please, that's exactly what","[{'question': 'would you like to see news about culpeper national cemetary', 'answer': 'yes including the history of the cemetary'}]",no i want their recipies
93,Information about raffles,F1047,Find information about car raffles.,are you trying to look up the results of a raffle in your area,similar_no_yes,"No, I want to learn about car raffles.","[{'question': 'are you interested in raffles college of design', 'answer': 'no i want a car raffle'}]",i am looking for a map that shows the political boundaries of brazil
10,Where can I find cheap internet,F0008,I want to find cheap DSL providers.,or maybe free internet,similar_yes_yes,I would like to know who has the lowest DSL price in my area.,"[{'question': 'are you looking for information on any specific internet technology', 'answer': 'yes i want to find inexpensive dsl providers'}]",im looking for nearby companies that do home appraisals
11,How to prepare for the GMAT?,F0046,I'd like to find some tips to help me do well on the GMAT.,would you like information on filing income taxes,off_topic,No I want info on how to prepare for the gmat.,"[{'question': 'are you looking for a specific web site', 'answer': 'i am looking for information on the gmat test to prepare'}]",no a simply map that a child could color
149,Tell me about uplift at yellowstone national park,F0191,home page for the Yellowstone Volcano Observatory,do you want to know what the current uplift is at yellowstone national park,similar_no_yes,no I want more information regarding the uplift at yellowstone national park,"[{'question': 'would you like to know trending data or a timeline for the uplift at yellowstone national park', 'answer': 'no im looking for the website for the yellostone volcano observatory'}]",i would like to know about available restaurants there
40,what are the popular jobs in Michigan,F0818,Find information about services available to the unemployed in Michigan.,do you need need information related to unemployed services in michigan,similar_yes_yes,Find information about services available to the enemployed in michigan.,"[{'question': 'would you like application information for the michegan works program', 'answer': 'yes'}]",no i would like directions to the ritz calton lake las vegas
135,Tell me about source of the nile,F0145,map of the Nile River basin,is there any specific information about the river that would interest you,similar_no_yes,"No, I just want the entire map of the Nile River Basin.","[{'question': 'are you interested in the origin of the nile', 'answer': 'no i want a map of the nile river basin'}]",no i would like to see some detailed geographic maps
182,How can I quick smoking,F0346,How can hypnosis help someone quit smoking?,do you want information about espn sports programming in languages other than english,off_topic,How can hyonosis help someone stop smoking?,"[{'question': 'do you want information on how many people successfully quit smoking', 'answer': 'no i am interested in information regarding methods for quitting smoking'}]",no just a list of movies about the civil war
78,I'm looking for information on dieting,F0979,Find recommendations for dieting and exercising.,will the dieting be in combination with exercise or weight training,similar_no_yes,Find recommendations for dieting.,"[{'question': 'do you want to learn about the history of dieting', 'answer': 'no i want recommendations of specific diets and which exercises to do'}]",no just the brands
31,Find information about atari,F0775,I am looking for a site where I can play old Atari games online.,do you want to book a stay here,off_topic,"No, I want to know where I can play atari games online.","[{'question': 'would you like to see a list of atari games', 'answer': 'no i am looking for a site where i can play the games'}]",no i just want to know the racing schedule at churchill downs
199,Tell me about fybromyalgia,F0406,What medicines can be used to treat fybromyalgia?,do you need mediciation for fibromyalgia,similar_yes_yes,I just want general information on fibromyalgia.,"[{'question': 'do you want information on treatments for fibromyalgia', 'answer': 'yes inparticular what medicines are used to treat fybromyalgia'}]",no just directions
141,How to register dmv in va?,F0168,Where are offices of the Virginia Department of Motor Vehicles located and what are their hours of operation?,which city in arkansas are you interested in,off_topic,Because he is asking for a city in Arkansas.,"[{'question': 'do you want to obtain forms from the dmv', 'answer': 'i dont know yet'}]",yes specifically about working as a computer programmer
148,What is martha stewart and imclone?,F0188,looking for information on Martha Stewart's involvement with ImClone,are you looking for a specific web site,similar_no_yes,"No, just general information.","[{'question': 'do you want to know who owns the company imclone', 'answer': 'no im looking for information about martha stewarts involvement with them'}]",yes cass county
189,Find information about the gs pay rate,F0371,Does the Federal Wage System affect the General Schedule?,do you need any specific information in relation with the federal wage system,similar_yes_yes,"Yes, I want to know how it affected the general schedule","[{'question': 'are you looking for the us civil servant pay scale', 'answer': 'yes i want to see the gs pay scale'}]",no i want to find political maps that include the states and their capitals
115,Tell me about the pacific northwest laboratory.,F0069,information about the scientific user facilities of the laboratory,are you looking for any specific facilities,similar_no_yes,information about the scientific user facilities of the laboratory.,"[{'question': 'are you looking for jobs in richland', 'answer': 'no i want information on pacific northwest laboratory facilities'}]",no just give me a listing of hoboken restaurants
236,tell me about symptoms of mad cow disease in humans,F0546,Find information about mad cow disease symptoms in humans.,do you have a specific toilet brand on your mind,off_topic,"no, i am talking about mad cow disease","[{'question': 'do you want to know if memory loss is a sign of mad cow disease', 'answer': 'im looking for all symptoms of mad cow disease'}]",no i am looking for an arcade game not a vehicle
78,I'm looking for information on dieting,F0979,Find recommendations for dieting and exercising.,are you searching for dieting pills,similar_yes_yes,No more just advice and recommendations on diet and exercise.,"[{'question': 'would you like a list of area doctors that can give professional advice on dieting', 'answer': 'yes that would be beneficial'}]",no i would like to know what it is
102,What is Fickle Creek Farm,F0017,Where can I buy products that come from Fickle Creek Farm?,are you looking for irons melting point,off_topic,I would like a full list of products available at Fickle Creek Farm.,"[{'question': 'do you want to know the location of fickle creek farm', 'answer': 'no i want ot find out where can i purchase fickle creek farm products'}]",yes im looking for online tutorials
15,Give me espn sports information.,F0195,I'm looking for information on NASCAR races.,do you want information about a specific espn sports program,similar_no_yes,"Yes, NASCAR live broadcast","[{'question': 'do you want espn sports corporate information', 'answer': 'no i want information on nascar races'}]",no i need to know if i can get their catalog products at their outlet stores
53,discovery channel store,F0872,Find Discovery Channel store products based on the Animal Planet program.,is there a specific product you are looking for from the store,similar_yes_yes,No just anything to do with Animal Planet.,"[{'question': 'shall i open discovery channel store homepage', 'answer': 'yes and find products based on animal planet'}]",i dont know
13,map,F0122,I want to find free printable maps.,are you trying to fix your toilet,off_topic,No I want to find free printable maps.,"[{'question': 'are you interested in cartography', 'answer': 'yes specifically where i can find free printable maps'}]",i would like to know what problems can happen with horseshoes
149,Tell me about uplift at yellowstone national park,F0189,"How likely is a volcanic eruption at Yellowstone National Park, and what would be the effects of such an eruption?",are you interested in a specific aspect of uplift at yellowstone national park,similar_no_yes,"Not really, I just want to know what the likelihood of eruption is.","[{'question': 'can i tell you about the north american plate that moves causing the eventual destruction of the volcano in yellowstone park', 'answer': 'no please tell me about the likeliehood and effects of an eruption'}]",general information
41,Looking for information about the Orange County Convention Center,F0820,How do I reserve the Orange County Convention Center for an event?,are you planning any events there,similar_yes_yes,"Yes, I would like to reserve space for an event I'm planning.","[{'question': 'do you want to know their hours of operation', 'answer': 'yes and how to reserve the convention center for an event'}]",no i am looking for reviews already posted about universal animal cuts
138,I'm looking for information on jax chemical company,F0152,contact information for Jax Chemical Company,do you need the address of jax chemical company,similar_no_yes,"Yes please, as this would be the most reliable way of communicating with the company.","[{'question': 'do you need info on what jax chemical company produces', 'answer': 'no i would like the contact information for the company'}]",no i am not looking for that information
87,who invented music,F1014,Who invented the radio?,do you have any type of asbestos in mind when you ask about the dangers of asbestos,off_topic,"No, I want to know who created the radio.","[{'question': 'are you interested in the invention of modern music or the beginning of all music', 'answer': 'no i want to know the inventor of the radio'}]",i want general information on the artwork used on rock music album covers
179,Tell me about black history.,F0327,Find a timeline for African Americans in the United States.,are you interesting in a certain countrys black history,similar_yes_yes,I am interested in the black history of the United States.,"[{'question': 'are you looking for black history figures', 'answer': 'yes and a timeline of african american history'}]",yes i am looking for information on the room price
88,Where can I find information about forearm pain?,F1018,Are there good home remedies for elbow pain?,are you looking for any specific web pages,similar_no_yes,"no, just give me any information you have about remedies for elbow pain.","[{'question': 'are you looking for causes of forearm pain', 'answer': 'no i am looking for good remedies for elbow pain'}]",no i am looking for information about the kentucky derby museum
65,Tell me about Korean language.,F0925,"Find a history of Hangul, the Korean writing system.",are you interested in schools in poterville,off_topic,"No, I want to learn about Hangul.","[{'question': 'are you looking for nearby classes', 'answer': 'no i want to read the history of hangul'}]",yes the homepage for the voyager learning programs
14,I'm interested in dinosaurs,F0159,"Go to the Discovery Channel's dinosaur site, which has pictures of dinosaurs and games.",are you looking for a specific web site about dinosaurs,similar_yes_yes,"Yes, I'd like to see the Discovery channels dinosaur website.","[{'question': 'are you looking for a dinosaur costume or game', 'answer': 'yes'}]",no i need the cass county mo budget for 2008
183,Tell me about kansas city mo,F0348,What hotels are near the Kansas City airport?,are you interested in visiting kansas city,similar_no_yes,"Ye, that's why I need hotel info.","[{'question': 'are you interested in upcomming events in kasas city mo', 'answer': 'no i need to know what hotels are near the kansas city airport'}]",yes i want to know where its native to
34,Tell me about cell phones.,F0789,What cell phone companies offer Motorola phones?,are you interested in a specific brand of cell phone,similar_no_yes,"Yes, specifically Motorola phones.","[{'question': 'were you looking for how cell phones work', 'answer': 'no i want to know what providers have motorola phones'}]",id like to know the different options for treating baldness
103,Tell me about madam cj walker,F0020,Find information about the business that C. J. Walker started.,would you like historical information on madam cj walker,similar_yes_yes,"Yes, and please include the name of the business that she started.","[{'question': 'do you want more information on the history of madam cj walker', 'answer': 'yes specifically information about the business that cj walker started'}]",yes the homepage for the voyager learning programs
196,Tell me information about a sore throat.,F0396,Find information on throat cancer.,would some analysis of hamlet be interesting to you,off_topic,"No, I want info on throat cancer please.","[{'question': 'are you wondering what causes sore throat', 'answer': 'no i would like any information on throat cancer'}]",yes but specifically in subject matter related to that day
154,figs,F0216,Find information on the different varieties of figs.,would you like to see a list of different kind of figs with images,similar_no_yes,Find information on the different varieties figs.,"[{'question': 'would you like to know where you can buy figs', 'answer': 'no i just want information on the variety of figs'}]",i need a map of the entire us capital
144,where can I buy a trombone?,F0175,information on where I could buy a new or used trombone,what year of volvo do you need information about,off_topic,"no, i am asking about trombones","[{'question': 'are you interested in selling or buying a trombone on amazon', 'answer': 'im looking for information about buying a used trombone'}]",yes
47,Tell me more about USA tax for annuity,F0841,What is an indexed annuity? What are their advantages and disadvantages? What kinds of indexed annuities are there?,do you want to know how much an indexed annuity would cost,similar_yes_yes,"sure, and also what is an indexed annuity?","[{'question': 'would you like to know the advantages and disadvantages of a indexed annuity', 'answer': 'yes'}]",yes where can i purchase a rock and roll poster
22,I'm looking for information on Rick Warren.,F0500,I want to see articles and web pages about the controversy over Rick Warren's invocation at the Obama inauguration.,are you trying to find more information about rick warren,similar_no_yes,"Yes, about his invocation at Obama's Inauguration.","[{'question': 'are you wanting to see videos by the pastor', 'answer': 'no i am looking for articles about him in regards to his invocation and president obamas inauguration'}]",no
58,Find information about penguins.,F0892,Find Pittsburgh Penguins merchandise such as hockey jerseys.,are you referring to the company or the term do not resuscitate,off_topic,i am referring to the penguins teams. i want merchandise.,"[{'question': 'what kind of penguin are you looking for', 'answer': 'this is not related to my search'}]",no
29,Tell me about ps 2 games?,F0730,Where can I find cheat codes for PlayStation 2 games?,are you referring to playstation 2 games,similar_yes_yes,"Yes, I need to know where I can find cheat codes for PlayStation 2 games.","[{'question': 'would you like to learn how to cheat in ps2 games', 'answer': 'yes but tell me where to find cheat codes'}]",im not looking for trains im looking for rc planes
11,How to prepare for the GMAT?,F0047,I'm looking for the BeatTheGMAT blog and forums.,do you want to know what madam cj walker is famous for,off_topic,No. How can I find the BeatTheGMAT blog and forums?,"[{'question': 'would you like to see a price range for gmat prep classes', 'answer': 'no i want to see the beatthegmat blog and forums'}]",yes cass county
124,Tell me about Bowflex Power Pro.,F0105,Find recall notices for the Bowflex Power Pro.,are you wondering if there has been a recall notice,similar_no_yes,"yes, i want to know about recalls for bowflex power pro","[{'question': 'do you want to know how to use the bowflex power pro', 'answer': 'no i need recall notices for the bowflex power pro'}]",no
17,I'm interested in poker tournaments,F0291,I want to find Texas Hold-Em tournaments.,would you like a schedule of poker tournaments,similar_yes_yes,Yes I would like to schdule poker tournaments but for Texas Holdem.,"[{'question': 'do you want to find local tournaments near you', 'answer': 'yes specifically tournaments for texas holdem'}]",i am looking for places to make such purchases
154,figs,F0214,Find information on nutritional or health benefits of figs.,are you interested in figs health benefits,similar_no_yes,Find information on nutritional or health benefits of figs.,"[{'question': 'if youre interested in recipes would you like savory or sweet receipes do you have other specific ingredients in mind', 'answer': 'no i jsut want nutritional information'}]",no id like to see an image of it
42,I’m looking for the music man.,F0823,Find current performances of The Music Man.,are you looking for information on the music man musical,similar_yes_yes,"Yes, information on the current performances of The Music Man.","[{'question': 'are you interested in the music man', 'answer': 'yes i am looking for current performances of the music man'}]",no i am looking for diseases and injuries in horse hooves not general information
28,I'm interested in InuYasha,F0699,"Find games based on the InuYasha series, either online or for game systems.",are you wondering where tornadoes are more likely,off_topic,find games based on the inuyasha series.,"[{'question': 'how would you like to watch inuyasha episodes', 'answer': 'are there any games that are based on inuyasha'}]",no i want to know how to host a show
186,tell me about UNC,F0361,Find reports of University of North Carolina Chapel Hill athletics.,are you interested in any specific activities at university of carolina,similar_yes_yes,Find reports of University of North Carolina Chapel Hill athletics.,"[{'question': 'would you like to learn about unc sports', 'answer': 'yes can you find reports'}]",yes specifically info about free activities and materials for running a diversity training program in an office
52,Tell me about avp,F0867,Find information about the Avon Products (AVP) company.,would you like information about the alternatives to violence project,similar_no_yes,No I want info about the Avon company.,"[{'question': 'are you looking for the stock symbol avp', 'answer': 'no i would like general information about avon company'}]",no im looking for the different brands of pressure washers
63,Find information about flushing.,F0915,Why do people blush? What is blushing?,do you want to know about a satellite receivers or dishes,off_topic,I want to know why people blush.,"[{'question': 'would you like to know about the plumbing mechanisms of flushing', 'answer': 'this is not related to my search'}]",no i would like to find reviews recipes and products
69,Find sewing instructions for me,F0941,Find helpful sewing tips for beginners.,are you wanting a copy of your credit report,off_topic,"No, I want tips on sewing for a beginner.","[{'question': 'would you like to know some basic tips for sewing', 'answer': 'yes beginner tips'}]",no just reviews and ratings
117,What are specific dangers of asbestos?,F0077,Find mortality rates due to asbestos exposure.,what kind of information are you looking for news or research on the dangers of asbestos,similar_yes_yes,"Yes, I would like to know the mortality rates.","[{'question': 'are you looking for some statistics regarding the exposure of asbestos', 'answer': 'yes the death rates related to asbestos exposure'}]",no i am looking for a walking map of hoboken new jersey
16,I'm looking for information about game and fish in Arizona.,F0239,What are the regulations for hunting and fishing in Arizona?,do you want to get a hunting or fishing license in arizona,similar_no_yes,Not really.  I want to learn about the regulations there.,"[{'question': 'would you like the arizona state fish and game comissions contact information', 'answer': 'no just information on hunting and fishing regulations'}]",no i want to make rock art
70,to be or not to be that is the question,F0946,"Find the text of Hamlet's famous ""To be or not to be"" soliloquy.",are you a dj,off_topic,I cannot say.,"[{'question': 'are you interested in shakespeares plays', 'answer': 'yes i would like to text from the to be or not to be soliloquy in hamlet'}]",yes i need room prices and availability
192,Find condos in Florida.,F0381,Find beachfront condos for sale in Florida.,do you want to be on the beach,similar_yes_yes,Yes. Please find condos for sale on the beachfront in Florida.,"[{'question': 'are you interested in condos in sale', 'answer': 'yes but only beachfront ones located in florida'}]",no i want to know what the capital gains tax rate is and how it is broken down
178,How to cook pork tenderlion,F0326,How do I grill a pork tenderloin on a gas grill?,do you need to cook a pork tenderloin,similar_no_yes,"Yes, and it needs to be on a gas grill.","[{'question': 'price of a pork tenderloin', 'answer': 'no i want to know how do i grill a pork tenderloin on a gas grill'}]",no i want to know where to buy radiocontrolled planes
88,Where can I find information about forearm pain?,F1020,Find information about supports and braces for the forearm to prevent injury or lessen pain.,do you want to know how a us president is elected,off_topic,No i want the information about his current leadership.,"[{'question': 'are you looking for causes of forearm pain', 'answer': 'no i want information about supports and braces'}]",i don know
16,I'm looking for information about game and fish in Arizona.,F0240,I'm looking for the Arizona Fishing Report site.,would you like the arizona state fish and game comissions contact information,similar_yes_yes,Yes where can i get that information in to detais?,"[{'question': 'would you like to see information on fishing in arizona', 'answer': 'yes the arizona fishing report'}]",yes the one for the city of hoboken nj
32,I'm looking for information on web design and hosting.,F0778,What are the cheapest web hosting companies? Who offers free web hosting?,are you interested in paid services,similar_no_yes,"Yes, as long as they are reasonably cheap.","[{'question': 'would you like to see reviews for website hosting and design companies', 'answer': 'no i would like to know which companies offer free or the cheapest web hosting'}]",yes
21,Tell me information about Volvo.,F0457,Find reviews of the Volvo XC90 SUV.,are you looking for the current performance of the music man,off_topic,Find reviews of the Volvo XC90 SUV.,"[{'question': 'are looking for reviews on volvo xc90 suv', 'answer': 'yes'}]",no im looking for more quotes like it
4,How to change the toilet in the house,F0813,How do I fix a toilet that isn't working properly?,do you need to repair your toilet,similar_no_yes,"Yes, I need instructions on how to repair it","[{'question': 'would you like to know the best way to clean a toilet', 'answer': 'no i need to know how to fix a broken toilet'}]",tell me about the problems that all models of ford edge have ever had
137,tell me about rock and gem shows,F0150,rock and gem shows that offer lapidary classes,would you like a list of rock and gem shows in 2019,similar_yes_yes,I want rock and gem shows in 2021 that offer lapidary classes.,"[{'question': 'are you interested in finding rock and gem shows near you', 'answer': 'yes'}]",no i want the newspaper rocky mountain news
186,tell me about UNC,F0360,What campuses are part of the University of North Carolina?,are you trying to look for kucoin shares cryptocurrency,off_topic,"no, i am looking for information about the campuses of university of north carolina","[{'question': 'are you interested in the whereabouts of the university of carolina', 'answer': 'yes specifically campus locations of the university of north carolina'}]",yes i need a home appraisal
87,who invented music,F1014,Who invented the radio?,would you like to know about inventions related to music,similar_no_yes,"yep, i want to know who invented the radio","[{'question': 'do you want to know what kind of music was the first', 'answer': 'no i want to know who invented the radio'}]",yes for coupons
52,Tell me about avp,F0865,Find the homepage for AVP antivirus software.,are you looking for irons melting point,off_topic,Just the homepage please.,"[{'question': 'would you like to know what avp stands for', 'answer': 'no i just want their homepage'}]",no only their native areas
168,What are the causes of lipoma tumors,F0282,What are the treatments for malignant lipolysis?,are you referring to malignant lipolysis,similar_yes_yes,"yes, and i want to know the treatments.","[{'question': 'do you need treatment information for lipoma', 'answer': 'yes'}]",no i want general guides tips and checklists for planning a wedding
67,I'm looking for information on VLDL levels,F0931,How are VLDL levels determined?,would you like things to do to soothe a sore throat,off_topic,"No, I want to learn how VLDL levels are determined.","[{'question': 'are you interested in information about the difference between vldl and hdl levels', 'answer': 'i want to know how they determine vldl levels'}]",yes a map ofthe inside of the us capitol
94,Give me information about Titan.,F1050,Find the homepage for Titan motorcycles.,are you referring to a specific vehicle,similar_yes_yes,I am referring to Titan motorcycles.,"[{'question': 'are you interested in a specific web page', 'answer': 'yes the hompage for titan motorcycles'}]",yes and i need to learn about rock painting
55,tell me about iron,F0880,What foods contain iron?,are you looking for a list of foods that are a good source of iron,similar_no_yes,"Yes, that would be good.","[{'question': 'do you want to know how to craft tools made of iron', 'answer': 'no i want to know what foods contain the mineral iron'}]",no i need the homepage for starbucks
13,map,F0124,I'm looking for an online world atlas.,which mountain ski resort would you like information around the pocono area,off_topic,I am not interested in this topic.,"[{'question': 'are you interested in satellite maps', 'answer': 'no i want an online world atlas'}]",no i am looking for reviews on their products
58,Find information about penguins.,F0891,Find the homepage of the Pittsburgh Penguins,are you looking for a specific web page,similar_no_yes,Show me information about the Pittsburgh Penguins,"[{'question': 'are you looking for some photos', 'answer': 'no i need the pittsburgh penguins homepage'}]",no what kind of solar cells are there
111,I'd like to learn about lymphoma in dogs,F0054,What are the symptoms of lymphoma in dogs?,are you looking for the current president of the united states,off_topic,No the symptoms of lymphoma in dogs please.,"[{'question': 'are you interested in the treatment costs of lymphoma in dogs', 'answer': 'no i neei to know what the symptons are'}]",no i would like to know who is the patron saint of mental illness
68,Find me information about PVC,F0935,What is the material PVC?,are you interested in pvc pipe,similar_no_yes,"No, I want to know what PVC is made out of.","[{'question': 'what project do you want to use the pvc for', 'answer': 'no i want information on what pvc is made of'}]",i just want pictures of horse hooves
185,How do I get my free annual credit report?,F0357,I need the customer service contact information for the three major credit reporting agencies.,do you want to know how to obtain someones credit report,similar_yes_yes,"no, i want phone numbers.","[{'question': 'would you like to know about credit scores', 'answer': 'yes specifically contact info to credit reporting agencies'}]",no
10,Where can I find cheap internet,F0009,Is there a way to get internet access without phone service?,would you like more information of the course of the yellowstone volcano and the different hypothesizes scientest have,off_topic,"No, I want to know how to get internet access without phone service.","[{'question': 'are you wondering who used cheap internet', 'answer': 'no i want internet package excluding phone service'}]",no i just want images of blue throated hummingbirds
153,Tell me about Pocono,F0210,Find general information on tourist activities in Pennsylvania's Pocono Mountains.,are you referring to pocono mountains,similar_no_yes,"Yes, but I want info on things for visitors to do in Pennsylvania's Pocono Mountains.","[{'question': 'would you like to know more about pocono raceway', 'answer': 'no i wanted to know more about the pocono mountains in pennsylvania'}]",yes
184,I’m interested in civil right movement,F0353,Find a timeline of the Civil Rights Movement in the United States.,do you want to know about specific key people,similar_yes_yes,Not necessarily. Just an overview of the timeline.,"[{'question': 'would you like to know what happened during the civil rights movement', 'answer': 'yes and how it originated and what is the history of the civil rights movement'}]",no
185,How do I get my free annual credit report?,F0357,I need the customer service contact information for the three major credit reporting agencies.,shall i take you to any specific pages of yahoo web site,off_topic,No I just need customer service contact information for three major credit reporting agencies.,"[{'question': 'wou you like to know more about 3in1 credit reports', 'answer': 'no'}]",i need best ways to dispose of dog waste
94,Give me information about Titan.,F1049,Find the homepage for Titan watches.,are you referring to the watch brand,similar_yes_yes,yes,"[{'question': 'are you interested in a specific web page', 'answer': 'yes i am interested in the homepage for the titan watches'}]",i just want to know if there are any
53,discovery channel store,F0869,Find the Discovery Channel store homepage.,shall i open discovery channel store homepage,similar_no_yes,"Yes, and tell me where to find the homepage.","[{'question': 'are you looking for locations', 'answer': 'no i am looking for the front page of the discovery channel website'}]",no i want you to find me the sports reporters for the rocky mountain news
113,Tell me more about HP mini 2140,F0060,"retailers, including price information, of the HP Mini 2140 notebook computer",is your question about tourism in vanuatu,off_topic,"no, i want to know pricing information for hp mini 2140.","[{'question': 'do you want to know the specs of hp mini 2140', 'answer': 'yeah i need to know who sells the hp mini 2140 notebook computer and for how much'}]",i dont know
3,How to get organised?,F0767,Find catalogs of office supplies for organization and decluttering.,are you referrring how to get organized,similar_no_yes,I am looking for supplies to do so.,"[{'question': 'are you looking to organize your course work', 'answer': 'no i want information on office supplies to help declutter and organize'}]",i am looking for who said the qoute provided
17,I'm interested in poker tournaments,F0287,I want to find information on the World Series of Poker.,are you looking for the world series of poker,similar_yes_yes,"Yes, I am.","[{'question': 'where would you like to find poker tournaments', 'answer': 'yes but in particular i would like any information onthe world series of poker'}]",would you like directions from your location
17,I'm interested in poker tournaments,F0287,I want to find information on the World Series of Poker.,where would you like to find poker tournaments,similar_no_yes,I would like find out about them anywhere.,"[{'question': 'do you want to know how poker tournaments are played', 'answer': 'no id like information on the world series of poker'}]",yes im looking for a picture of that
43,Find information about the secret garden.,F0828,I'm looking for biographical notes about Frances Hodgson Burnett.,can i provide you information about frances hodgson burnett,similar_yes_yes,"Yes, I want biological notes about her.","[{'question': 'is the secret garden a book you are interested in', 'answer': 'yes i am interested in the author of the book the secret garden'}]",yes
160,What are the best recepies for grilling,F0242,Find kabob recipes.,are you wanting to see sermons by the pastor,off_topic,"no, i want kebab recipes","[{'question': 'do you want to see cookbooks for grilling', 'answer': 'im just looking for recipes now not to buy a cookbook'}]",i would like to know about the citys zoning regulations
137,tell me about rock and gem shows,F0151,information on clubs that host rock and gem shows,are you looking for information about upcoming rock and gem shows,similar_yes_yes,"Yes, and I would like to know about their venues.","[{'question': 'would you like to know about rock and gem shows in washington', 'answer': 'yes also please provide any other rock and gem show clubs'}]",i am only looking for the bluethroated hummimgbird
183,Tell me about kansas city mo,F0348,What hotels are near the Kansas City airport?,are you looking for bedroom furniture,off_topic,No show me hotels that are in the area of the Kansas City aiport,"[{'question': 'would you like to see a map of kansas city mo', 'answer': 'no i want to see hotels near kansas city airport'}]",i need a website with reviews for the ritz carlton lake
150,How can one can become highway patrol,F0200,I want to fill in the customer satisfaction survey about my interaction with a Tennessee Highway Patrol State Trooper.,are you interested to fill a survey for them,similar_no_yes,No I need to complete a survey due to being pulled over by the State Trooper with the Tennessee Highway Patrol.,"[{'question': 'did you want to be informed as to whre the tennesse highway patrol academy is located', 'answer': 'no just customer satisfaction forms'}]",i would like to know how it could be treated
144,where can I buy a trombone?,F0176,good places to sell a used trombone,would you like to see music stores in your area,similar_yes_yes,yes,"[{'question': 'are you looking for a store that sells trombones near you', 'answer': 'yes i need a used trombone'}]",i want to find online sellers
111,I'd like to learn about lymphoma in dogs,F0054,What are the symptoms of lymphoma in dogs?,are you looking for a list of er actors,off_topic,"no, tell me about lymphoma symptoms in dogs","[{'question': 'do you want to know the nearest vet that can help', 'answer': 'no what are the symptoms of lymphoma in dogs'}]",yes i need room prices and availability
89,Give me information on OCD.,F1022,What are the symptoms of obsessive-compulsive disorder?,do you want to know the symptoms of ocd,similar_no_yes,"Yes, what are the symptoms?","[{'question': 'are you interested in ocd medications', 'answer': 'no i am interested in the symptoms'}]",no i am looking for reviews already posted about universal animal cuts
162,Tell me more about dnr,F0254,What are the Maryland Department of Natural Resources' regulations for deer hunting?,do you mean the department of natural resources,similar_no_yes,"Yes, can you tell me what rules they have for hunting deer?","[{'question': 'would you like to fill an application for a hunting licence', 'answer': 'no i want to know more about deer hunting regulations in maryland'}]",no i am looking for voyager learning programs no the voyager space mission
4,How to change the toilet in the house,F0815,I'm looking for a Kohler wall-hung toilet. Where can I buy one?,are you purchasing pork tenderloin today,off_topic,This isn't related to my search.,"[{'question': 'what type of toilet are you looking for', 'answer': 'a kohler wallhung toilet'}]",no i need information on diversity training and activities
1,Tell me about Obama family tree.,F0003,Find biographical information on Barack Obama's mother.,do you want to know more about obamas parents,similar_yes_yes,"Yes, particularly his mother.","[{'question': 'would you like to know about obamas ancestors', 'answer': 'yes specifically his mother'}]",no i need the nutritional information for the starbucks menu
171,Tell me about ron howard.,F0299,What television shows did Ron Howard act in?,would you want to know about ron howards acting career,similar_no_yes,"Yes, particularly his television roles.","[{'question': 'do you want to know how old ron howard is', 'answer': 'no id like to learn what tv shows he was in'}]",no i want to know the name of elvis presleys home
147,tell me about tangible personal property tax,F0184,When is the tangible personal property tax due?,are you talking about a psychology book,off_topic,When is the tangible personal property tax due?,"[{'question': 'would you like to see a list of states which receive tangible personal property tax', 'answer': 'no please tell me when the tangible personal property tax is due'}]",no
115,Tell me about the pacific northwest laboratory.,F0066,"career opportunities at PNL: what openings are currently available, what educational background is required, what prior experience is needed",are you referring to the specific company,similar_yes_yes,"Yes, Pacific Northwest Laboratory.","[{'question': 'do you need information on employment opportunities', 'answer': 'yes i would like to know what is available and if i need a specific degree to work pnl'}]",no im looking for retailers that sell pc memory
9,I am looking for sources of used car parts.,F1028,I'm looking for the car-part.com web site.,do you want to obtain used car parts,similar_yes_yes,"Yes, I want to look for them on the website car-part.com","[{'question': 'do you want to sell used car parts', 'answer': 'yes i need a website to buy used car parts'}]",no i want to know what the capital gains tax rate is and how it is broken down
148,What is martha stewart and imclone?,F0188,looking for information on Martha Stewart's involvement with ImClone,are you interested in martha stewarts role in the company,similar_no_yes,"Yes, I would like to know the connections between the two.","[{'question': 'do you want to know if martha stweart works for the company', 'answer': 'no i am looking for information regarding the connections between martha stewart and imclone'}]",i want to know about nanotechnology in solar panels
55,tell me about iron,F0882,Find information about the element iron (Fe).,are you looking for irons melting point,similar_no_yes,"Yes, and other things about iron in general.","[{'question': 'are you looking to buy an iron for your clothes', 'answer': 'no i need information about the element iron'}]",no estate listings
162,Tell me more about dnr,F0253,What is required to get a hunting license online from the Michigan Department of Natural Resources?,do you mean the department of natural resources,similar_yes_yes,"Yes, the Michigan Department of Natural Resources.","[{'question': 'would you like to know more about hunting rules', 'answer': 'yes would like more information on how to obtain a hunting license as well as hunting rules'}]",no
91,Tell me about er television show.,F1035,Find summaries of episodes from the show ER.,are you interested in summaries of episodes of er tv show,similar_no_yes,"Yes, I would like more information on that topic","[{'question': 'do you want to know awards er has won', 'answer': 'no i want to find summaries of episodes'}]",no i need an example of emplyee performance appraisals
129,Tell me information about Iowa's food stamp program,F0120,Find statistics for the food stamp program in Iowa.,are you looking for more information on food stamps in iowa,similar_no_yes,"yes, give me statistics about the food stamp program in iowa.","[{'question': 'would you like directions to the nearest iowa food stamp office', 'answer': 'no i need statistics for the program'}]",yes jewelry
120,TV on computer,F0089,Looking for information on how to watch television programming on your computer.,do you want to find online tv streaming services,similar_yes_yes,i want to know how i can watch tv on my computer.,"[{'question': 'are you looking for netflix', 'answer': 'yes and another options'}]",maybe i want to find reviews about it first
40,what are the popular jobs in Michigan,F0817,Find career resources and information on job seeking in Michigan.,would you like help searching for work in michigan,similar_yes_yes,"Yes, mainly career resources and job seeking.","[{'question': 'can i take you to the resource page at the michworks website', 'answer': 'yes please show me the resources page'}]",no
99,Tell me more about satilies,F1069,Find providers of satellite internet service.,are you inquiring about satellite tv,similar_no_yes,"no, i want to know providers of satellite internet.","[{'question': 'are you referring to satellite imagery on google maps', 'answer': 'no i am looking for stelitte internet service'}]",i want informaion on the ontario ca airport ammendities
38,How can I adopt a dog,F0805,What should I know about adopting a dog?,are you willing to adopt a shelter dog,similar_yes_yes,"Yes, what do I need to know to make an adoption","[{'question': 'would you like to see local spca or humane societies', 'answer': 'yes'}]",no i just need the seating chart
151,What is a 403b?,F0202,Who is eligible for a 403b plan?,would you like to see resources for retirement investing,similar_yes_yes,"Yes, at least the eligility for a 403b plan.","[{'question': 'are you looking for the information how 403b plan works', 'answer': 'yes i would like to know who is eligible for one'}]",no
21,Tell me information about Volvo.,F0459,Find a Volvo dealer.,are you looking for a specific web site,similar_no_yes,"No, just a Volvo dealer near me.","[{'question': 'are you asking what year the company originated', 'answer': 'no i am just looking for a dealer'}]",no
217,Tell me about kids earth day activities,F0491,What are fun activities kids can do to celebrate Earth Day?,do you want to know more about kid safe earth day activities,similar_yes_yes,What are fun activities kids can do to enjoy and celebrete Earth day?,"[{'question': 'are you looking for craft ideas for kids on earth day', 'answer': 'yes these would be a good start'}]",no i want to know the history
121,Tell me about the sit and reach test.,F0093,"Find out what the ""sit and reach test"" is.",do you want general information about the test,similar_yes_yes,Yes.,"[{'question': 'do you want to know the purpose of the test', 'answer': 'yes and what is the test specifically'}]",no i am looking for the service and facilites offered by the ontario canada airport
75,Find information about tornadoes,F0963,"Find information about tornadoes, what causes them, and where they occur.",are you interested in how tornadoes are formed,similar_no_yes,"Yes, I also want to know where tonrnadoes occur","[{'question': 'are you interested in tornado safety', 'answer': 'no i am interested in where tornadoes occur and what causes them'}]",i need a printable map
36,Which gps receiver I should buy,F0797,Find reviews of GPS units and car navigation systems.,are you looking for car navigators,similar_no_yes,"yes, gps and car navigation reviews","[{'question': 'would you like to know your gps coordinates', 'answer': 'no i want reviews for handheld ups units and portable car navigation systems'}]",no estate listings
80,I'm looking for keyboard reviews,F0989,Find reviews of computer keyboards.,would you like information on this years keyboards,similar_yes_yes,"Yes, but I specifically want to read reviews for the keyboards.","[{'question': 'are you interested in electronic keyboard reviews', 'answer': 'yes'}]",no im looking for information about the website for the city of hoboken nj
119,How to write a thank you letter after an interview?,F0083,Find examples of thank-you letters for sending after an interview.,would you like to know more about writing interview thank you letters,similar_no_yes,"Indeed yes, that will greatly help for example. thank you letter.","[{'question': 'do you want guidelines on how to ace an inteview', 'answer': 'no just examples of post0interview thank youb letters'}]",i need to know what hobby stores carry trains
189,Find information about the gs pay rate,F0370,Find the General Schedule pay tables.,do you need any specific information in relation with the federal wage system,similar_no_yes,general pay tables,"[{'question': 'would you like to see a gs salary calculator', 'answer': 'no i would like to see the gs pay tables'}]",no i want to know what is the best way to get rid of dog waste
129,Tell me information about Iowa's food stamp program,F0117,Find general information about Iowa's food stamps program.,would you like a website about this topic,similar_yes_yes,Yes if the website has info on food stamps in Iowa.,"[{'question': 'are you looking for more information on food stamps in iowa', 'answer': 'yes is there a website to view'}]",i would like information on starbucks nutrition and caolorie count
67,I'm looking for information on VLDL levels,F0931,How are VLDL levels determined?,would you like information about cholesterol reports,similar_no_yes,"No, I want to see how VLDL levels are determined.","[{'question': 'would you like to see charts about vldl levels', 'answer': 'no i would like to know how the levels are determined'}]",yes
180,Tell me about hotels in New York.,F0338,I want to book a room in a hotel that's on Times Square in New York City.,would you like to book a new york hotel,similar_yes_yes,"Yes, a hotel that's on Times Square.","[{'question': 'do you need help finding your new york hotel', 'answer': 'yes i need to book a room'}]",yes id like information about nasa voyager missions
92,Find information about the wall,F1041,"Find sites devoted to the Vietnam Veterans Memorial, such as virtual tours and databases of names inscribed on the wall.",are you referring to the vietnam veterans memorial wall,similar_no_yes,"Yes, give me a website with a database of the names on the wall.","[{'question': 'do you want to know the news about the border wall', 'answer': 'no i want web sites about the vietnam veterans memorial'}]",no i need the site where i can determine room price and availability
78,I'm looking for information on dieting,F0976,Find tips and charts for counting calories while dieting.,would you like to know more about dieting products for weight loss,similar_yes_yes,"Yes, specifically about counting calories.","[{'question': 'will the dieting be in combination with exercise or weight training', 'answer': 'yes but i also need charts and tips for calorie counting while im on a diet'}]",yes specifically how to build adobe houses
159,Find information on Porterville.,F0237,Find the homepage of the Porterville Recorder newspaper.,is there any specific web page on your mind,similar_no_yes,"Yes, I want the homepage of the Porterville Recorder newspaper webpage.","[{'question': 'are you looking for a hotel near porterville', 'answer': 'no i want the website for the porterville recorder newspaper'}]",no
135,Tell me about source of the nile,F0144,information on the feud between Speke and Burton over the discovery of the source of the Nile river,do you want a map,similar_yes_yes,"No, not a map, I only want information on the feud between Speke and Burton.","[{'question': 'are you referring to the nile river', 'answer': 'yes i want information on the feud between speke and burton over the discovery of the source of the river'}]",no i am interested in whether they can prediect cervical cancer
103,Tell me about madam cj walker,F0019,Find historical information about Madam C. J. Walker.,do you want to know what madam cj walker is famous for,similar_yes_yes,Yes.,"[{'question': 'would you like to know the birthplace of madam cj walker', 'answer': 'yes'}]",yes i want to know who said it and why
46,Give me information about Alexian Brothers hospitals.,F0838,Go to the Alexian Brothers Health System homepage.,do you need their homepage,similar_no_yes,Yes.,"[{'question': 'are you looking for the alexian brothers lay catholic order', 'answer': 'no thats not the alexian brothers that im looking for'}]",no i want to find thepowerwasheradvisorcom website
63,Find information about flushing.,F0915,Why do people blush? What is blushing?,do you want to know why your face is flushing,similar_no_yes,I am interested in why people's faces begin to blush. Why do they do it?,"[{'question': 'are you looking for a specific product in flushing queens', 'answer': 'no i want to know what makes people blush'}]",no not the video game i need the defender marine supplies homepage
170,Tell me about scooters.,F0293,Find kids' scooters for sale.,are you looking for locations that have the scooters,similar_yes_yes,"Yes, I am looking for the best place for scooters at a reasonable price.","[{'question': 'there are some cool deals available shall i show them', 'answer': 'yes please'}]",no i would like the archives of the articles in the milwaukee journal sentinel
81,Tell me about Afganistan.,F0992,"Find information about Afghanistan's history, government, religion, and culture.",would you like historical information about afghanistan,similar_no_yes,Yes.,"[{'question': 'are you looking for current news about afghanistan', 'answer': 'no i want historical information on government culture and religion'}]",no a different kind of business establishment but not hotels
14,I'm interested in dinosaurs,F0162,"I'm looking for a list of all (or many of) the different kinds of dinosaurs, with pictures.",are you looking for dinosaur books,similar_yes_yes,"no, i just want a list of names of dinosaurs.","[{'question': 'do you want a list of dinosaur names', 'answer': 'yes i would also like the list to include pictures of the dinosaurs'}]",no i would like to find the homepage for the city of hoboken nj
28,I'm interested in InuYasha,F0697,I'm looking for pictures and wallpaper images from InuYasha.,would you like to see inuyasha manga,similar_no_yes,"No, I just want pictures and wallpapers for my computer background.","[{'question': 'would you like to watch an inuyasha movie', 'answer': 'no im looking for inuyasha pictures and wallpapers'}]",yes i am looking for example of poems to carry
124,Tell me about Bowflex Power Pro.,F0106,Find a retailer from whom I can buy a Bowflex Power Pro.,would you like to know where to buy one,similar_no_yes,"Yes, let me know what stores sell this Bowflex product.","[{'question': 'would you like to learn more about how to exercise with the bowflex power pro', 'answer': 'no i am looking for a retailer to buy the bowflex power pro not how to use it'}]",no i am looking for information on the mathematician euclid
86,tell me about bart sf,F1008,Find BART train schedules and fares.,are you looking for bart travel schedules,similar_yes_yes,yes please find me the bart schedules and ticket prices.,"[{'question': 'are you looking for a specific web site', 'answer': 'yes the bart one that has train schedules and fares'}]",no i just want a list of the reporters who write the sports for the rocky mountain news
12,how to hire disc jockey,F0087,How do I become a radio disc jockey?,would you like to read about dj employment,similar_yes_yes,How do i become a radio disc jockey?,"[{'question': 'would you like to know how to become a dj', 'answer': 'yes i would like to know how to become a dj'}]",i want to know what hotels are near
88,Where can I find information about forearm pain?,F1016,Find pages or sites that describe the anatomy of the forearm.,do you have forearm pain from typing,similar_no_yes,"no, i don't have pain. i just need information about forearm anatomy.","[{'question': 'does your forearm hurt from sports', 'answer': 'no im looking for the anatomy of the forearm'}]",i just want to see the home page of rocky mountain news
181,I’m interested in old coins,F0341,What is the value of a rare wheat US penny?,is there a specific type of coin that interests you,similar_yes_yes,"Yes, a United States wheat penny.","[{'question': 'would you like information on the worth of coins', 'answer': 'yes i want to know the worth of a rare wheat us penny'}]",yes but i would like more general information about ascus cells
167,Tell me about Barbados.,F0273,Find a map of Barbados.,are you interested in barbados,similar_no_yes,"Yes, I need to see a map of barbados.","[{'question': 'would you like to know about david thompson', 'answer': 'no i need to find a map of barbados'}]",no
173,Find information on hip fractures,F0305,Find information on hip fractures in the elderly.,are you interested in the age breakdown of common hip fracture sufferers,similar_yes_yes,"No, just hip fractures with old people.","[{'question': 'are you interested in treatments for hip fractures', 'answer': 'yes and other information on hip fractures that occur in the elderly'}]",yes
112,Is Kenmore heater good,F0059,retailers of and price information for Kenmore gas water heaters,are you iinterested in a kenmore gas water heater,similar_no_yes,"Yes, who are some retailers who sell it, and what are the prices.","[{'question': 'are you troubleshooting or trying to repair the unit', 'answer': 'no i am looking to purchase'}]",i am not interested on that topic
121,Tell me about the sit and reach test.,F0093,"Find out what the ""sit and reach test"" is.",do you want to know the purpose of the test,similar_yes_yes,Yes.,"[{'question': 'do you want to know how to perform this test', 'answer': 'yes id like to know about this test'}]",the political jurisdictions
52,Tell me about avp,F0863,"Go to the homepage for the AVP, sponsor of professional beach volleyball events.",would you like information about the association of volleyball professionals,similar_no_yes,No I just want the homepage of AVPS.,"[{'question': 'do you want to know how male vs female avps in a company', 'answer': 'no i want avps homepage'}]",no i am looking for information about human memory
173,Find information on hip fractures,F0306,How do you treat a hip fracture and what is the prognosis for recovery?,do you need info on remedies,similar_yes_yes,"Yes, I would.","[{'question': 'do you want to know what the symptoms of a hip fracture are', 'answer': 'yes and treatment'}]",yes
32,I'm looking for information on web design and hosting.,F0781,"Find reviews of web hosting services, geared towards small business needs.",are you interested in paid services,similar_no_yes,"Yes, as long as they are cost effective.","[{'question': 'would you like to take some courses on web design', 'answer': 'no i need a web hosting service that is geared towards small businesses'}]",no i am interested in salaries
121,Tell me about the sit and reach test.,F0095,How is the sit and reach test properly done?,are you looking for information on how its scored,similar_yes_yes,"No, I'm looking for information on how it's properly executed.","[{'question': 'do you want to know how to perform this test', 'answer': 'yes i do'}]",just general information about them
109,I'm looking for information about mayo clinic Jacksonville FL,F0040,"What medical services are available at the Mayo Clinic in Jacksonville, FL?",would you like to know more about the mayo clinic facilities and services,similar_no_yes,i want to know what kind of medical services i can get there.,"[{'question': 'are you looking for outpatient services in mayo clinic', 'answer': 'no im looking for all medical services'}]",no
129,Tell me information about Iowa's food stamp program,F0120,Find statistics for the food stamp program in Iowa.,are you looking for more information on food stamps in iowa,similar_no_yes,"Yes, more specifically the statistics of the food stamps.","[{'question': 'are you looking for a specific web site', 'answer': 'no i want statistics for the food stamp program in iowa'}]",no i want to know how to care for them
96,tell me about rice?,F1055,Find biographical information about former Secretary of State Condoleeza Rice.,are you referring to a person named rice,similar_yes_yes,"yes, condoleeza rice.","[{'question': 'are you interested in a specific web page', 'answer': 'yes her biographty'}]",i need to build them not find them
178,How to cook pork tenderlion,F0324,Find recipes for pork tenderloin marinades and dry rubs.,would you like to make a rub for pork tenderloin,similar_yes_yes,"Yes, I would like to.","[{'question': 'would you like to see pork tenderloin recipes', 'answer': 'yes i would like pork tenderloins recipes that use dry rub or marinades'}]",no i am not interested in that topic
16,I'm looking for information about game and fish in Arizona.,F0241,I'd like to find guides and outfitters for hunting trips in Arizona.,would you like information on arizona wildlife,similar_yes_yes,"Yes, but particularly guides and outfitters for the practice of hunting.","[{'question': 'would you like to see arizona hunting trip information', 'answer': 'yes i want to look at more information about arizona huntings trips'}]",yes
80,I'm looking for keyboard reviews,F0991,What computer keyboards are best for gaming?,do you just want to rated keyboards,similar_no_yes,i want to know which ones are good for gaming,"[{'question': 'would you like information on this years keyboards', 'answer': 'no i need to know the best gaming keyboards'}]",no i want information on where the stores are located
160,What are the best recepies for grilling,F0242,Find kabob recipes.,do you want more informaiton about grilling vegtables,similar_no_yes,I need the recipe to make kabob specifically,"[{'question': 'do you need to know where you can purchase a grill', 'answer': 'no i am looking for kabob recipes for the grill'}]",maybe
146,What can I do in sherwood regional library,F0181,What are the hours of operation of the Sherwood Regional Library?,do you want to know the hours of operation,similar_yes_yes,"I would, of the library, yes.","[{'question': 'would you like to see the hours of the sherwood regional library', 'answer': 'yes i would'}]",i want to kno wthe calorie count of each item
65,Tell me about Korean language.,F0924,Find resources on learning and teaching Korean.,are you looking for books on the korean language,similar_yes_yes,Sure if they'll teach me the Korean language.,"[{'question': 'are you trying to learn the korean language', 'answer': 'yes'}]",no i am looking for retail stores that sell stone carving tools
140,Information about east ridge high school.,F0165,"information about the sports program at East Ridge High School in Clermont, Florida",are you looking for east ridge high school activities,similar_no_yes,"Yes, sports activities specifically.","[{'question': 'are you interested in east ridge high school latest news', 'answer': 'no im interested in information about the sports program at east ridge high school'}]",yes that would be helpful
22,I'm looking for information on Rick Warren.,F0497,Take me to Rick Warren's homepage.,are you looking for a specific web page,similar_yes_yes,Yes the home page of Rick Warren.,"[{'question': 'do you know someone named rick warren', 'answer': 'yes take me to his homepage'}]",no im looking for reviews
70,to be or not to be that is the question,F0948,"Find a critical analysis of Hamlet's ""To be or not to be"" soliloquy.",are you interested in the quote from hamlet,similar_no_yes,"no, give me a critical analysis of Hamlet","[{'question': 'do you want to know where the quote came from', 'answer': 'no i want a critical analysis'}]",no i want to know more about the ritz carlton lake las vegas resort
176,Tell me about weather stripping,F0317,What is the best way to seal or weather strip my garage door?,would you like to learn about weather stripping,similar_yes_yes,"As I said before, yes, for my garage door.","[{'question': 'do you want to learn how to install weather strips on doors', 'answer': 'yes installing on my garage door'}]",yes and any other general information about memory that you have
70,to be or not to be that is the question,F0946,"Find the text of Hamlet's famous ""To be or not to be"" soliloquy.",are you interested in the quote from shakespeare or the quote used in another context,similar_yes_yes,"Find the text of Helmlets famous,","[{'question': 'do you want to know where the quote came from', 'answer': 'yes'}]",i dont know
69,Find sewing instructions for me,F0940,Find downloadable sewing patterns.,can you read sewing patterns,similar_no_yes,Yes but I need some downloadable sewing patterns.,"[{'question': 'would you like instructions on how to use a sewing machine', 'answer': 'no i need sewing patterns'}]",no i want to see road maps of the us
179,Tell me about black history.,F0327,Find a timeline for African Americans in the United States.,are you interested in black history,similar_yes_yes,"yes, i am. i want a timeline of black history.","[{'question': 'are you interested in history in the united states', 'answer': 'yes specifically african american history'}]",no
1,Tell me about Obama family tree.,F0001,"Find the TIME magazine photo essay ""Barack Obama's Family Tree"".",are you referring to the time magazine essay,similar_yes_yes,"Yes, the one about Barack Obama's Family Tree.","[{'question': 'would you like to know about obamas ancestors', 'answer': 'yes this is what am looking for'}]",yes and other video guides or books on how to build one
58,Find information about penguins.,F0891,Find the homepage of the Pittsburgh Penguins,are you looking for a specific web page,similar_no_yes,Just like what I said before.,"[{'question': 'are you interested in where penguins live', 'answer': 'no i want the hompage of the penguins hockey team'}]",the airport can be found at 2500 east airport drive
10,Where can I find cheap internet,F0007,Find me some providers of free wireless internet access.,are you wondering which provider has the cheapest internet,similar_yes_yes,i want to know which providers have free wireless internet access.,"[{'question': 'are you interested in lowcost internet providers', 'answer': 'yes i am looking for low cost internet providers'}]",yes but i would also like information about all hayrides in pennsylvania
188,Tell me about Internet phone serices.,F0369,How much does internet phone service cost?,are you interested in price comparison of packages,similar_no_yes,"Yes, but I want prices for your internet and phone services.","[{'question': 'do you need information on residential or business', 'answer': 'i dont know i want to know the cost'}]",no i want to know what the us capital tax rate consists of and how it is broken down
9,I am looking for sources of used car parts.,F1027,I'm looking for online sites that sell car parts.,are you looking for a specific web site,similar_yes_yes,"No, I want to view a wide range of sites that sell used car parts.","[{'question': 'would you like to know maore about getting the best used car parts', 'answer': 'yes i need an online site that sells used car parts'}]",i dont know
109,I'm looking for information about mayo clinic Jacksonville FL,F0041,"How does one request an appointment at the Mayo Clinic in Jacksonville, Florida?",which department are you interested in at mayo clinic jacksonville fl,similar_yes_yes,I just want to request an appointment.,"[{'question': 'would you like to request an appointment', 'answer': 'yes'}]",yes i want a map of the area around the us capitol including nearby sites to visit
60,Tell me about Bellevue.,F0902,"Find information about Bellevue, Nebraska.",do you want to know about the nearest town named bellevue,similar_yes_yes,"Yes please, info on Bellevue.","[{'question': 'do you need information about bellevue nebraska', 'answer': 'yes i do'}]",no i want to know what von willebrand disease is
13,map,F0123,I want to find sources for satellite maps and live satellite photos.,are you interested in satellite maps,similar_no_yes,"Yes, I want information on where to get maps or photos by operational satellites","[{'question': 'do you want a map with driving directions', 'answer': 'no i want satellite maps'}]",no i need demographic information
148,What is martha stewart and imclone?,F0186,find sites that support Martha Stewart with respect to the insider trading case,would you be interested in learning more about martha stewart and imclones history,similar_yes_yes,"Yes, and websites that support her.","[{'question': 'are you interested in martha stewarts role in the company', 'answer': 'yes i would like to know martha stewarts role in imclone'}]",yes i am looking for general information on kiwi fruit
30,Find me information about diabetes education,F0770,Take me to the American Association of Diabetes Educators homepage.,are you looking for a specific web site,similar_no_yes,"Yes , I was eagerly waiting for that website for having some amount of information about it","[{'question': 'are you searching for prevention tools', 'answer': 'no i want the homepage for the american association of diabetes educators please'}]",no i am looking for information on the greek mathematician euclid
94,Give me information about Titan.,F1050,Find the homepage for Titan motorcycles.,are you interested in a specific titan,similar_no_yes,i want to know the homepage only.,"[{'question': 'are you interested in learning more about mythological titans', 'answer': 'no i am interested in titan motorcycle company'}]",yes i am looking for breeders cup races
87,who invented music,F1011,Find information on the history and development of music.,would you like to know about inventions related to music,similar_yes_yes,"No, just the history and development of music.","[{'question': 'do you want to know what kind of music was the first', 'answer': 'yes as well as how music developed from that point onward'}]",english i need a blackandwhite map that a kid could color in
182,How can I quick smoking,F0344,What are the benefits of quitting smoking?,are you trying to quit smoking,similar_no_yes,Yes. I would like to know the immediate benefits I would experience.,"[{'question': 'are you looking for doctors that can help you quit smoking', 'answer': 'no i want information on what are the health benefits of quitting smoking'}]",no i need their web site please
29,Tell me about ps 2 games?,F0731,I'm looking for sites that announce new PlayStation 2 games.,are you referring to playstation 2 games,similar_yes_yes,Yes I am.,"[{'question': 'would you like to see a list of new released ps2 games', 'answer': 'yes i would like to see newly released ps2 games'}]",yes tell me what congenital conditions causes it
63,Find information about flushing.,F0916,"Find a street map of Flushing, NY.",are you referring to flushing new york,similar_no_yes,"yes, show me a street map","[{'question': 'are you looking for a directions to the new york hall of science in flushing meadows corona park', 'answer': 'no i am looking for a map of the flushing neighborhood area only'}]",no im not
88,Where can I find information about forearm pain?,F1020,Find information about supports and braces for the forearm to prevent injury or lessen pain.,are you looking for any specific web pages,similar_yes_yes,"No, just information about supports and braces for my forearm to prevent injury or help treat pain.","[{'question': 'are you looking for a specific method to cure your forearm pain', 'answer': 'yes supports and braces for the pain'}]",no not really
58,Find information about penguins.,F0892,Find Pittsburgh Penguins merchandise such as hockey jerseys.,would you like to buy some stuff related pittsburgh penguins,similar_no_yes,"Yes, I'm looking for things like jerseys.","[{'question': 'would you like to buy a book about this topic', 'answer': 'no im looking for pittsburh penguins merchandise'}]",na
96,tell me about rice?,F1056,What is the nutritional value of white rice?,do you want to know how to harvest rice,similar_yes_no,No just the nutritional content of it.,"[{'question': 'do you want to know the nutritional content of rice', 'answer': 'yes i want to know the nutritional value of rice'}]",no im looking for websites that do appraisals
28,I'm interested in InuYasha,F0699,"Find games based on the InuYasha series, either online or for game systems.",are you interested in inuyasha wiki activity,similar_no_no,"No, I am looking for video games based off the Inuyasha series.","[{'question': 'are you looking for any specific pictures', 'answer': 'no i am looking for inuyasha games'}]",no not the game just general information on the human memory
55,tell me about iron,F0884,Find dealers in irons for clothing.,would you like to know how iron is mined,similar_no_no,"No, I need to buy an iron for smoothing out clothes.","[{'question': 'are you interested in knowing how iron is made', 'answer': 'no i need to find places to buy irons for clothing'}]",i need facility information on the ontario ca airport
50,Info on dog heat?,F0856,What are symptoms of heat stroke and other heat-related illnesses in dogs?,do you want to know how long a female dogs heat lasts,similar_yes_no,"No, heat strokes in dogs, not a dog in heat.","[{'question': 'what would you like to know about the dog heat season', 'answer': 'yes'}]",no i dont need examples
55,tell me about iron,F0882,Find information about the element iron (Fe).,woud you like a list of items made from iron,similar_no_no,Sure.,"[{'question': 'would you like to figure out iron alloys used to make stainless steel', 'answer': 'no i would like general information about the element iron'}]",no one i want to know the symptoms
111,I'd like to learn about lymphoma in dogs,F0053,What treatments are available for dogs diagnosed with lymphoma?,would you like to know about risk factors of lymphoma in dogs,similar_yes_no,"No, I need treatments available for dogs with lymphoma.","[{'question': 'are you looking for treatment options', 'answer': 'yes for lymphoma in dogs'}]",yes thats right
11,How to prepare for the GMAT?,F0048,Take me to the VeritasPrep home page.,would you like to know what distinguishes gmat from gre,similar_no_no,"No, I want to be taken to the VeritasPrep homepage.","[{'question': 'would you like to know more about the gmat test', 'answer': 'no i want the veritasprep home page'}]",no
187,Tell me about vanuatu,F0365,"Find photos from the ""Survivor 9, Vanuatu"" TV reality series.",are you interested in visiting,similar_no_no,"No, I want photos from the Survivor episode.","[{'question': 'do you want to know the history', 'answer': 'no i am looking for photos from season nine of the television show survivor'}]",no i am looking for a road map of the united states
180,Tell me about hotels in New York.,F0336,Find inexpensive hotels in New York City.,what is your price range,similar_yes_no,Just go ahead and list them from the lowest price first.,"[{'question': 'do you need a list of available new york hotels', 'answer': 'yes the least expensive ones'}]",no i want to know the historical information about orcas island
21,Tell me information about Volvo.,F0459,Find a Volvo dealer.,are you interested in who is the ceo,similar_no_no,"No, I am interested in the new crossovers.","[{'question': 'would you like to buy semi truck', 'answer': 'no i need a volvo dealer'}]",no
182,How can I quick smoking,F0344,What are the benefits of quitting smoking?,are you looking for patches,similar_yes_no,"No, I want to know why I should quit, what are the benefits of ditching cigarettes?","[{'question': 'are you trying to quit smoking', 'answer': 'yes'}]",none i would like the sports section of the milwaukee journal sentinel
151,What is a 403b?,F0203,What are the rules for a 403b retirement plan?,are you trying to find out the difference between 401k and 403b,similar_yes_no,Not really. What are the rules of a 403b?,"[{'question': 'do need to see any specific information about 403b eligibility', 'answer': 'yes i need to know the rules'}]",yes i need this information
179,Tell me about black history.,F0329,Find names of famous African American inventors.,do you want to know about a specific person,similar_no_no,"no, just famous African American Inventors in general.","[{'question': 'are you looking for a specific event or activity', 'answer': 'no i would like to find names of famous african american inventors'}]",no i need info about the show star trek voyager
15,Give me espn sports information.,F0193,I want to find NBA basketball standings.,do you wnat sports scores,similar_yes_no,I want to find NBA basketball standings.,"[{'question': 'are you looking for information on a specific league', 'answer': 'yes i need nba standings'}]",yes
22,I'm looking for information on Rick Warren.,F0499,I'm looking for background and biographical information on Rick Warren.,are you wanting to see videos by the pastor,similar_yes_no,"Yes, show me videos of Rick Warren's life","[{'question': 'are you referring to the pastor', 'answer': 'yes id like background information on rick warren'}]",yes show me reports on ford edges reliability
87,who invented music,F1014,Who invented the radio?,are you interested in the invention of modern music or the beginning of all music,similar_no_no,I am interested in the invention radio.,"[{'question': 'do you want to know the first song ever recorded', 'answer': 'no i would like to know who invented the radio'}]",no im looking for information on how often they can predict cancer
75,Find information about tornadoes,F0965,What were the deadliest tornadoes in history?,do you need to know the difference between a watch and a warning,similar_yes_no,"No, I'd like to know what the deadliest tornadoes in history were.","[{'question': 'are you interested in tornado disasters', 'answer': 'yes i want to know which tornadoes were the deadliest'}]",no find the sports section
167,Tell me about Barbados.,F0273,Find a map of Barbados.,would you like the latest news of barbados,similar_yes_no,"No, I would like to see a map of it.","[{'question': 'would you like a map of barbados', 'answer': 'yes'}]",no i am looking for reviews of the ritz carlton lake las vegas
170,Tell me about scooters.,F0294,Find the homepage of Hoveround scooters.,are you looking to rent a scooter,similar_no_no,No I want the hoveround scooters homepage,"[{'question': 'are you interested in scooter laws', 'answer': 'no i want to find the homepage of hoveround scooters'}]",no just a list of movies on the civil war
158,How should I use the septic system design,F0232,I need a septic system contractor.,are you looking for septic system design software,similar_yes_no,Not the software. I need an engineer.,"[{'question': 'are you looking for engineers in such field', 'answer': 'yes i am looking for a sepetic system engineer'}]",no just reviews and ratings
28,I'm interested in InuYasha,F0701,Find music from the InuYasha television series.,are you interested in a specific season of inuyasha,similar_no_no,"No, what I had just said before.","[{'question': 'are you interested in the list of inuyasha characters', 'answer': 'no i am interested in music for the inuyasha television series'}]",no information about hosting on the pampered chef cooking show
176,Tell me about weather stripping,F0318,How do I weather strip my sliding glass door?,would you like to know what a weather strip is,similar_yes_no,"No, as I said I need to know how to install on a sliding glass door.","[{'question': 'do you want to learn how to install weater strips on windows', 'answer': 'yes i need information on installing weather strips on large sliding glass windows or doors'}]",i would like to know the illinoise state income tax
162,Tell me more about dnr,F0252,"What are ""do not resuscitate"" orders and how do you get one in place?",are you referring to the the department of natural resources in maryland,similar_yes_no,"No, I am interested in ""do not resuscitate"" orders.","[{'question': 'are you interested in the medical term dnr', 'answer': 'yes i want to know what dnr orders are and how to get one in place'}]",i dont know
167,Tell me about Barbados.,F0275,Suggest tourist activities in Barbados.,are you looking for a specific website,similar_no_no,"Yes, website about tourist activities in Barbaros","[{'question': 'are you interested in barbados flag', 'answer': 'no i need to find tourist activities'}]",are you interested in computer memory
55,tell me about iron,F0881,Find sites where I can buy iron supplements.,are you trying to determine whats a safe amount of iron in your blood,similar_yes_no,No I need to find a place online where I can buy iron supplements.,"[{'question': 'would you like to buy supplements', 'answer': 'yes i would like to find a site to buy iron supplements'}]",no i want to find the webpage
148,What is martha stewart and imclone?,F0185,find information/timeline about Martha Stewart's insider trading case,do you want to know who owns the company imclone,similar_no_no,"Not really, I only want to know information about Martha Stewart's insider trading.","[{'question': 'are you interested in martha stewarts role in the company', 'answer': 'not necessarly unless it has to do with the insider trading case'}]",i need to find a spreadsheet to figure it out
78,I'm looking for information on dieting,F0975,"Find ""reasonable"" dieting advice, that is not fads or medications but reasonable methods for weight loss.",would you like to know more about dieting products for weight loss,similar_yes_no,"no, i want real dieting advice","[{'question': 'are you looking for dieting that involves no medications', 'answer': 'yes i would like information about dieting that requires no medications'}]",no im looking for the history of hoboken
161,Tell me about furniture for small spaces.,F0249,What is the effect of mirrored surfaces in small spaces?,are you interesting in buying furniture,similar_no_no,"No, I'm simply looking for information about mirrored surfaces in small places for now.","[{'question': 'are you looking for living room furniture', 'answer': 'no i would like to know the effect of mirrored surfaces in small places'}]",yes id like to read those reviews
151,What is a 403b?,F0203,What are the rules for a 403b retirement plan?,would you like to see resources for retirement investing,similar_yes_no,"No, just the rules for a 403b retirement plan.","[{'question': 'would you like to know more about a 403b retirement account', 'answer': 'yes i want to know the laws surrounding it'}]",yes
62,Tell me about texas border patrol.,F0912,How do I get a job with the U.S. Border Patrol in Texas?,do you want to know what their jurisdiction is,similar_no_no,No I want to know how to apply for a job.,"[{'question': 'are you trying to find out if they can use deadly force', 'answer': 'no i want to work for them'}]",yes
109,I'm looking for information about mayo clinic Jacksonville FL,F0042,"Find the contact information for the Mayo Clinic in Jacksonville, FL.",are you wanting to visit this hospital because of a friend or family,similar_yes_no,"no, address","[{'question': 'would you like to know more about the mayo clinic facilities and services', 'answer': 'yes tell me the ratings mayo clinic facilities and services'}]",no just what they offer
196,Tell me information about a sore throat.,F0397,What does it mean when my throat is sore on only one side?,are you looking for doctors that treat sore throats,similar_no_no,"No, I just want to know why my throat feels the way it does.","[{'question': 'would you like things to do to soothe a sore throat', 'answer': 'no i want to know why my throat is only sore on one side'}]",no im looking for migration patterns
187,Tell me about vanuatu,F0364,I need travel and tourism information for Vanuatu.,do you want to contact somebody here,similar_yes_no,"no, i want general travel information.","[{'question': 'do you want to know the population', 'answer': 'yes and nother local information'}]",yes from starbucks
91,Tell me about er television show.,F1036,Find episodes of ER I can download or watch online.,are you looking for a list of er episodes,similar_no_no,yes,"[{'question': 'are you interested in summaries of episodes of er tv show', 'answer': 'no i need to find er episodes i can download or watch online'}]",no i need more information on nanotechnological solar power
141,How to register dmv in va?,F0168,Where are offices of the Virginia Department of Motor Vehicles located and what are their hours of operation?,would you like the phone numbers to the va dmv registration,similar_yes_no,"no, i need the locations and when they are open","[{'question': 'would you like hours for va dmv registration', 'answer': 'yes i would like to know the hours but i also need to know their locations'}]",yes but also how to manage a diverse work force
70,to be or not to be that is the question,F0947,Find famous quotes from Shakespeare's plays.,do you want to know how others have used that quote,similar_no_no,"no, i want to know more famous quotes from him","[{'question': 'are you referring to the philosopher aristotole', 'answer': 'no im talking about shakespeare'}]",i am looking for where i can get euclid truck parts
88,Where can I find information about forearm pain?,F1017,What are some exercises recommended for forearm pain?,are you looking for any specific web pages,similar_yes_no,"No, I want to find information on exercises to help with forearm pain.","[{'question': 'does your forearm hurt from sports', 'answer': 'yes what exercises can i do to ease the pain'}]",the symptoms
91,Tell me about er television show.,F1035,Find summaries of episodes from the show ER.,do you want to know what time er tv show is on,similar_no_no,"No, as I said I just need summaries of episodes.","[{'question': 'are you looking for the featured music on the er tv show', 'answer': 'no i am looking for summaries of episodes from the show er not featured music from the show'}]",no i am not
53,discovery channel store,F0872,Find Discovery Channel store products based on the Animal Planet program.,are you looking for a certain store location,similar_yes_no,"no, i want animal planet products from discovery channel store","[{'question': 'are you looking for a deadliest catch product', 'answer': 'yes i am looking for products but not from deadliest catch'}]",i dont know
67,I'm looking for information on VLDL levels,F0933,"What is the difference between LDL, HDL, and VLDL?",would you like to take a survey on your cholesterol,similar_no_no,"I'm just interested in the difference between LDL, HDL and VLDL?","[{'question': 'what age range would you like to see recommended vldl levels for', 'answer': 'no can you just tell me the difference between vldl and ldl and hdl'}]",yes specifically what were the major battles
263,tell me about evidence for evolution,F0635,What are the current scientific theories of and data on evolution?,are you looking for evolution of people,similar_yes_no,just evolution in general,"[{'question': 'are you looking for scientific evidence', 'answer': 'yes'}]",no i want to know how to care for them
60,Tell me about Bellevue.,F0904,Find the homepage of Bellevue University.,are you looking for bellevue baptist church,similar_no_no,"No, the university, I'm looking for the home page of Bellevue University.","[{'question': 'would you like to see notable residents of bellevue washington', 'answer': 'no take me to the bellevue university homepage'}]",no i am looking for examples of wedding budgets
234,tell me about dark chocolate health benefits,F0539,What are the health benefits associated with eating dark chocolate?,are you trying to loss weight,similar_yes_no,Information need reminder.,"[{'question': 'did you need the nutritional value for dark chocolate', 'answer': 'yes that would be helpful'}]",no i want to know worldwide locations
122,Tell me more about Culpeper National Cemetry,F0098,Where is the Culpeper National Cemetery located?,are you looking for things to do near culpeper national cemetery,similar_no_no,"No, I want to find out the location of the site.","[{'question': 'do you want to know the history of culpeper national cemetery', 'answer': 'no i want to know the location'}]",i want to find i dead for how to celebrate poeam in your pocket day and national poetry month
5,Find information about Mitchell College.,F0854,Find information on admissions to Mitchell College. How do I become a student there?,would you like directions to mitchell college,similar_yes_no,how can i become a student at mitchell college?,"[{'question': 'are you interested in a specific web page', 'answer': 'yes i am looking for the admissions page to mitchell college'}]",the demographic info for cass county mo
162,Tell me more about dnr,F0254,What are the Maryland Department of Natural Resources' regulations for deer hunting?,do you want to know the legality of dnr,similar_no_no,i want to know rules about deer hunting in maryland,"[{'question': 'are you interested in the medical term dnr', 'answer': 'no i want to know the regulations related to deer hunting by maryland department of natural resources'}]",no
65,Tell me about Korean language.,F0925,"Find a history of Hangul, the Korean writing system.",are you interested in korean language degrees,similar_yes_no,"no, i want to know about the history of hangul","[{'question': 'are you looking for information about hangul', 'answer': 'yes i want to read about its history'}]",no
30,Find me information about diabetes education,F0768,"Find free diabetes education materials such as videos, pamphlets, and books.",do you want help finding a medical doctor for diabetes education,similar_no_no,No just info in the form of books and pamphlets.,"[{'question': 'are you searching for prevention tools', 'answer': 'no i want free education materials'}]",no i just want to know about average salaries
186,tell me about UNC,F0361,Find reports of University of North Carolina Chapel Hill athletics.,are you interested in the whereabouts of the university of carolina,similar_yes_no,"No, I want to read reports on their athletics.","[{'question': 'would you like to learn about unc sports', 'answer': 'yes can you find reports'}]",no i only want to know about one particular person
86,tell me about bart sf,F1010,Find a site that automatically plans trips on the BART system.,do you need to purchase a bart ticket,similar_yes_no,"No not yet, I just need to plan trips.","[{'question': 'do you need information on how to ride the bart', 'answer': 'yes i need details on how to travel around on bart'}]",no thanks
129,Tell me information about Iowa's food stamp program,F0120,Find statistics for the food stamp program in Iowa.,regarding food stamps in iowa are you looking for eligibility information,similar_no_no,"no, I want what I last asked for.","[{'question': 'are you interested in the requirements for applying to the program or the poverty level limits', 'answer': 'no i want the statistics of then iowa food stamp program'}]",none
181,I’m interested in old coins,F0342,I'm looking for information about old US silver dollars.,would you like information on the worth of coins,similar_no_no,Yes that's it.,"[{'question': 'do you want pictures of old coins', 'answer': 'no i need resouces that will give me information on old coins and their value'}]",yes and i am also looking for road maps
187,Tell me about vanuatu,F0364,I need travel and tourism information for Vanuatu.,do you want to contact somebody here,similar_yes_no,Yes if they can give me travel info.,"[{'question': 'is your question about tourism in vanuatu', 'answer': 'yes'}]",yes i would like information about their anatomy
77,Information about bobcat,F0974,Find the homepage of the Bobcat company.,are you interested in cultivated or wild bobcats,similar_no_no,"No, I need the webpage for the Bobcat company.","[{'question': 'are you looking for a specific tractor model', 'answer': 'no just the website'}]",no i want to know how adobe houses are built
138,I'm looking for information on jax chemical company,F0155,Who are retailers that sell Jax Chemical Company's Green Patina solution?,do you need info on what jax chemical company produces,similar_yes_no,"Yes, specifically their green patina solution.","[{'question': 'are you interested in a specific type of product', 'answer': 'yes i am looking for green patina solution'}]",none i would like the sports section of the milwaukee journal sentinel
42,I’m looking for the music man.,F0822,Find lyrics for songs from The Music Man.,do you want to know the actors in the music man,similar_no_no,"no, I want to know the lyrics of the songs from The Music Man.","[{'question': 'are you looking for reviews of the music man', 'answer': 'no i am looking for the music man lyrics'}]",no
3,How to get organised?,F0767,Find catalogs of office supplies for organization and decluttering.,are you looking to organize your course work,similar_yes_no,"Yes, any sort of organization.","[{'question': 'do you need tips on diy organizational methods', 'answer': 'yes i need office supplies that will help me organize and declutter my office'}]",i do not know how to answer the quest
115,Tell me about the pacific northwest laboratory.,F0067,types of research projects performed at PNL,do you need stock price values for the company,similar_no_no,"no, I want to know which research projects pnl does.","[{'question': 'is there any specific information that you would like to know about employment requirements at pnl', 'answer': 'no i am looking for types of research projects performed at pnl'}]",i just need the ontario ca airports address
88,Where can I find information about forearm pain?,F1019,Find information about tendinitis in the forearms.,are you looking for a specific method to cure your forearm pain,similar_yes_no,i just need general information about tendinitis,"[{'question': 'does your forearm hurt from twisting', 'answer': 'yes what information on forearm tendinitis can you give me'}]",i need to know which carry trains
58,Find information about penguins.,F0895,"Find pictures of the penguins from the animated movie, ""Madagascar"".",would you like to buy some stuff related pittsburgh penguins,similar_no_no,"No, I want pictures of the penguins from the movie ""Madagascar"".","[{'question': 'are you looking for a specific web page', 'answer': 'no i want to see images of penguins from the madagascar movie'}]",i dont know
186,tell me about UNC,F0361,Find reports of University of North Carolina Chapel Hill athletics.,would you like to learn about the unc campuses,similar_yes_no,"No, I would like to learn about their athletic reports.","[{'question': 'are you interested in any specific activities at university of carolina', 'answer': 'yes athletics'}]",no ingredients im looking for a complete recipe for stroganoff
189,Find information about the gs pay rate,F0371,Does the Federal Wage System affect the General Schedule?,do you want to know the federal pay cap for 2018,similar_no_no,"No, I'm actually looking to find out how the wage system affects the general schedule.","[{'question': 'are you interested in applying for federal jobs', 'answer': 'no i am interested in knowing if the federal wage system affects the general schedule not in applying for jobs'}]",no i want to find information on which tribes built adobe houses
185,How do I get my free annual credit report?,F0358,How do you dispute credit report information?,are you wanting a copy of your credit report,similar_yes_no,No I just want to know how to disupte the credit report info.,"[{'question': 'are you interested in learning if your credit report is safe', 'answer': 'yes'}]",yes
185,How do I get my free annual credit report?,F0358,How do you dispute credit report information?,would you want to know what is in a credit report,similar_no_no,"no, i want to know how to dispute credit report if something is wrong","[{'question': 'may i provide you a list of best credit reporting agencies', 'answer': 'no how do i dispute credit report information'}]",i am interested in general treatment for severe angular cheileitis
167,Tell me about Barbados.,F0276,Find the Barbados Underground homepage.,are you interested in barbados,similar_yes_no,I'm interested specifically in barbados underground.,"[{'question': 'would you like a map of barbados', 'answer': 'yes i would like to see a geographical map of barbados'}]",no i want to know some poems that were written for poem in your pocket day
113,Tell me more about HP mini 2140,F0061,product reviews for the HP Mini 2140 notebook computer,do you need technical specifications for the hp mini 2140,similar_no_no,Nope just the product reviews for it.,"[{'question': 'do you want to know the specs of hp mini 2140', 'answer': 'no i am looking for reviews on the hp mini 2140 notebook computer'}]",i would like to know who said that quote
145,Tell me about vines for shade.,F0178,"ideas on using plant vines to shade an area on or around my house from the sun, like training them on an inexpensive trellis or up a wall or fence",what growing climate do you live in,similar_yes_no,I live in a humid subtropical climate.,"[{'question': 'do you want to know how to plant a vine for shade', 'answer': 'yes'}]",im looking for flight information for the ontario ca airport
188,Tell me about Internet phone serices.,F0366,What is the best internet phone service?,are you looking for a free internet phone service,similar_no_no,I am looking for the best internet phone service,"[{'question': 'is there a specific internet company you need information on', 'answer': 'no i want to know about which one is the best'}]",i dont know i think i am more interested in current information
42,I’m looking for the music man.,F0824,Find recordings of songs from The Music Man.,are you looking for showtimes for the music man,similar_yes_no,Yes tell me what songs are from the music man.,"[{'question': 'do you want to listen to songs from the music man', 'answer': 'yes'}]",yes so i would like to know where can i buy a road map of brazil
188,Tell me about Internet phone serices.,F0367,Find free internet phone service.,do you need technical support related to your service,similar_no_no,No I just need to find a free phone service.,"[{'question': 'are you looking into price difference of companies in your area', 'answer': 'no i am looking for free internet phone service specifically'}]",no which indian tribes lived in them
78,I'm looking for information on dieting,F0979,Find recommendations for dieting and exercising.,do you need anything specific in relation to counting calories you consume daily,similar_yes_no,"yes, I would like to know more about that topic","[{'question': 'are you looking for dieting tips', 'answer': 'yes and exercise tips as well'}]",yes i am interested in the history of orcas island
40,what are the popular jobs in Michigan,F0817,Find career resources and information on job seeking in Michigan.,would you like application information for the michegan works program,similar_yes_no,"no, i do not.","[{'question': 'are you looking for michworks career information', 'answer': 'yes please'}]",no i would like more information about nasa voyager
52,Tell me about avp,F0868,"Find sites devoted to the ""Alien vs. Predator"" movie franchise.",do you want an acronym meanining for avp,similar_no_no,"No, I am want to know about the movie of Alien vs. Predator.","[{'question': 'do you want to know about a management position', 'answer': 'no i want to see sites about alien vs predator'}]",no i need to know how do they treat carotid cavernous fistula or ccft
182,How can I quick smoking,F0343,What are the ways you can quit smoking?,are you looking for smoking alternative products,similar_yes_no,Yes or ways to quit cold turkey.,"[{'question': 'are you looking for information on how to quit smoking', 'answer': 'yes'}]",yes the racing schedule
168,What are the causes of lipoma tumors,F0278,What are the causes of lipoma tumors in humans?,are you looking for the definition to lipoma,similar_no_no,"No, that's not relevant","[{'question': 'are you referring to malignant lipolysis', 'answer': 'no i am trying to find out what causes lipoma tumors in humans'}]",i need information about antique appraisals
160,What are the best recepies for grilling,F0245,Find instructions for grilling chicken.,do you need to know where you can purchase a grill,similar_yes_no,"No, I am not interested in the topic","[{'question': 'are you interested in grilling a specefic food', 'answer': 'yes chicken'}]",no i want to know what von willebrand disease is
58,Find information about penguins.,F0894,Find penguin photos.,do you want to watch funny penguin videos,similar_yes_no,"no, pictures","[{'question': 'are you looking for any specific information about the birds', 'answer': 'yes i need photos of them'}]",i dont know
196,Tell me information about a sore throat.,F0396,Find information on throat cancer.,are you looking for medicines to treat a sore throat,similar_no_no,"No, I want to know about throat cancer","[{'question': 'are you wanting to know the illnesses that list sore throat as a symptom', 'answer': 'no i want information on throat cancer'}]",no i need the internet homepage for euclid chemical company
63,Find information about flushing.,F0913,"Find information about Flushing, a neighborhood in New York City.",would you like directions to flushing new york,similar_no_no,"No, I am interested in finding information about flushing out a wound.","[{'question': 'would you like to see diagrams of how a toilet flushes', 'answer': 'no i am not intrested in this information'}]",no
40,what are the popular jobs in Michigan,F0818,Find information about services available to the unemployed in Michigan.,are you searching for workers for your company,similar_yes_no,"No, I am looking for services for unemployed in Michigan.","[{'question': 'do you need help navigating the website', 'answer': 'yes for services availalble to the unemployed'}]",no i just want to go to the starbucks homepage
94,Give me information about Titan.,F1051,"Find information about Saturn's moon, Titan.",are you referring to the titans from titanfall,similar_yes_no,"No, I mean Titan the moon of saturn","[{'question': 'are you referring to titan the moon of saturn', 'answer': 'yes find information about it please'}]",yes but i also need more general onformation about solar panels too
30,Find me information about diabetes education,F0769,Take me to the NIH National Diabetes Education Program homepage.,are you wanting to join a diabetes education gtoup,similar_no_no,No find me diabetes education information on the NIH national diabetes education program homepage,"[{'question': 'are you searching for prevention tools', 'answer': 'no i want to go to the homepage for the nih diabetes education program'}]",yeah the breeders cup
30,Find me information about diabetes education,F0772,How can I become a diabetes educator?,are you looking for a specific web site,similar_yes_no,"No, I just want to find out how to be a diabetes educator.","[{'question': 'are you wanting to find a class on the education of the disease of diabetes', 'answer': 'yes that is helpful'}]",i want to know about issues that tend to affect ford edge vehicles
155,Find me information about the Last Supper painting.,F0219,"Are tickets available online to view da Vinci's Last Supper in Milan, Italy?",do you want to know who painted the last supper painting,similar_no_no,"I already know who painted it, I just want to buy tickets to the exhibit.","[{'question': 'do you need directions to see the last supper painting', 'answer': 'no i want to buy tickets'}]",no i want to know about injuries and diseases
137,tell me about rock and gem shows,F0150,rock and gem shows that offer lapidary classes,would you like directions to local rock and gem shows,similar_no_no,"Yes, if they offer lapidary classes.","[{'question': 'would you like to know about rock and gem shows in washington', 'answer': 'no just show me all rock and gem shows that offer lapidary classes'}]",no
78,I'm looking for information on dieting,F0978,Find herbal diet supplements and appetite suppressants.,are you interested in reading more about the health benefits of dieting,similar_yes_no,"Not necessarily, I just want to know about available herbal diet pills.","[{'question': 'are you searching for dieting pills', 'answer': 'yes specifically herbal ones'}]",i am looking for online promotional coupons for brooks brothers
172,I'm looking for information on becoming a paralegal,F0301,What training is required to become a paralegal?,do you want a paralegal internship,similar_no_no,First I want information on the necessary training,"[{'question': 'would you like to know more about the duties of a paralegal', 'answer': 'no i want to know about the training a paralegal has'}]",no i want to know who said it
21,Tell me information about Volvo.,F0458,Where can I find Volvo semi trucks for sale (new or used)?,are you interested in who is the ceo,similar_yes_no,"No, I want to find a vehicle for sale.","[{'question': 'do you need information about a volvo dealership', 'answer': 'yes this will help'}]",no im asking about the different brands of pressure washers
62,Tell me about texas border patrol.,F0912,How do I get a job with the U.S. Border Patrol in Texas?,would you like to know how many there are,similar_no_no,"No, I would like to see if they are hiring.","[{'question': 'are you looking for a specific web page', 'answer': 'no but i want to find one with job information'}]",no i just want their current home page
68,Find me information about PVC,F0934,Find information about PVC pipes and fittings.,are you looking to buy pvc pipe,similar_yes_no,"No, first I need info about PVC pipes and their fittings.","[{'question': 'are you looking for methods on how to repair leaks in pvc pipe', 'answer': 'yes'}]",yes and i need information also about cervical caner and hpv
141,How to register dmv in va?,F0169,home page of the Virginia Department of Motor Vehicles,do you want a list of departments within the va dmv registration,similar_no_no,"No, I just want the website for the VA DMV.","[{'question': 'are you interested in organ donation information', 'answer': 'no i need to go to the virginia dmv homepage'}]",no i am interested in the tv series
88,Where can I find information about forearm pain?,F1020,Find information about supports and braces for the forearm to prevent injury or lessen pain.,are you worried your forearm pain means you have a broken bone,similar_yes_no,Find information about support to prevent forearm or prevent injury or less pain.,"[{'question': 'are you having forearm pain', 'answer': 'yes what forearm supports and braces can ease the pain'}]",im just looking for a list of pressure washer brands
183,Tell me about kansas city mo,F0351,"Find information on the Hallmark Visitors Center in Kansas City, MO.",would you like to know about things to see and do in kansas city mo,similar_no_no,"Yes, but I'd also like information on the Hallmark Visitors Center.","[{'question': 'are you looking for casinos in kansas city missouri', 'answer': 'no i want to know about the hallmark visitors center'}]",no i want to know historical facts about cass county missouri not information about schools
94,Give me information about Titan.,F1051,"Find information about Saturn's moon, Titan.",are you referring to the monster from the final fantasy series,similar_yes_no,"No. I'm referring to Saturn's moon, which is named Titan.","[{'question': 'are you interested in a specific titan', 'answer': 'yes i am specifically interested in saturns moon'}]",no i just want to know which indian tribes constructed them
2,Find information on French Lick Resort and Casino.,F0408,What jobs are available at French Lick Casino and Resort?,do you have a preference of the casino in french lick,similar_no_no,"No, I want to know what jobs are available there.","[{'question': 'would you like to see all listings for casinos in french lick', 'answer': 'no i need to know the available jobs at french lick casino and resort'}]",no i want to know if universal animal cuts are safe and effective
185,How do I get my free annual credit report?,F0359,How is a credit score determined?,would you want to know what is in a credit report,similar_no_no,"Yes, what is contained in the report that affects the score?","[{'question': 'do you want information on what is in a credt report', 'answer': 'no im looking specifically to how its determined'}]",yes exactly
144,where can I buy a trombone?,F0175,information on where I could buy a new or used trombone,are you looking for a place to sell a used trombone,similar_yes_no,No I don't need to sell my used one. I'm giving it away. I just want to buy a trombone right now.,"[{'question': 'are you looking for discounted trombines', 'answer': 'yes i am but i just need to buy one'}]",no i want to find thepowerwasheradvisorcom website
173,Find information on hip fractures,F0307,How many hip fractures occur annually in the US?,do you want to know how to treat the injury,similar_no_no,"No, simply the statistics on the number of hips fractures that occur annually.","[{'question': 'are you interested in the age breakdown of common hip fracture sufferers', 'answer': 'no i want to know how many hip fractures occur on an annual basis'}]",yes and other info
59,how to build a fence?,F0899,Where can I buy materials for building a fence?,are you looking for instructions to build a fence,similar_no_no,"No, I want to know where I can find the materials.","[{'question': 'are you looking for companies to build a fence for you', 'answer': 'no i would like to find retail stores where i can purchase materials for a fence'}]",no
119,How to write a thank you letter after an interview?,F0084,How can I best end a job interview positively?,would you like to know more about writing interview thank you letters,similar_no_no,"with pleasure , I want to know about it ,please tell me","[{'question': 'would you like a list of common interview questions', 'answer': 'no i want to find out how to best end a job in a manner that delivers a postive outcome'}]",no i am trying to understand more about cultural diversity and prejudice
